 <jobs>
    <publisher-name>Resourcing Group</publisher-name>
    <publisher-url>http://www.resourcinggroup.us/</publisher-url>
    <job>
        <id>788</id>
        <date>2019-11-27 20:03:00</date>
        <title>Construction Project Manager - Healthcare</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=788&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            We are seeking an Healthcare Project Manager for an exciting role with a large General Contractor who work in New York. As a Project Manager you will be an integral part of leading contractor working in their Healthcare Division. Be a part of the most dynamic and fast paced market sectors in the construction industry. Responsibilities:Manage projects and a team consisting of Architects, Engineers, Contractors, and specialty vendorsOversee all aspects of construction and renovations projects within a healthcare environmentAssemble a project scope of work, budget estimates, and schedulesTrack and monitor project financials, schedules, and changesSolicitation, bidding, negotiating and selection and management of architects, engineers, contractors, FF&amp;E, technology and equipment vendorsCandidate will be working on both Architectural and Infrastructure M.E.P. projectsManage construction specialty and medical equipment installation vendorsPerform Construction administration functions; contract performance, inspections, oversee commissioningOn-Site design and construction investigation and coordination work for smooth project integration and deliveryRepresent client and interact and communicate with all project stakeholders and end usersCoordinate interaction with NYS DOH and NYC regulatory agencies for project permits, inspections, and approvalsPosition may be dedicated at one client site full time or may be managing multiple projects at different sites Required Skills:Minimum of 5 years of project management experience, specifically in Healthcare construction field and/or building.A four (4) year degree in engineering, architecture, building construction, or a related field or higher.ASHE HCC, OSHA 30, CCM, or PMP certification a plusStrong interpersonal, communication and writing skills, extreme attention to detail and ability to manage multiple tasks.Travel to multiple client locations and daily client/vendor interaction.MS Office and Project experience; Primavera 6/MS Project/e-Builder/Unifier experience is a plus.Must be able to fulfill essential job functions in a consistent state of alertness and safe manner.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Project Manager </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>787</id>
        <date>2019-11-26 22:49:04</date>
        <title>Regional Facilities Manager</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=787&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>50,001 – 75,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Brooklyn, New York</location>
        <description>
            Integrated Facilities Manager FirmFacilities Manager $50,00 - $60,000 Resourcing Group is working with a leading facilities firm, a company who provides facility solutions to multiple industries in the United States. The company offers steady maintenance, emergency/restoration, and security and concierge services, as well as specialized cleaning and construction services, including exterior maintenance, landscaping, mid-construction, and post-construction cleaning. Specialist sectors include; Office complexes, government and municipal complexes, university campuses, residential, retail, medical, and sports and entertainment to name only a few. We are seeking a qualified and experienced Facility Manager who will manage, oversee and supervise the staff responsible for maintaining various facilities within their key sectors.Responsibilities Include:Ensuring that facilities are is being maintained in line with the client's specific instructions and necessities.Inspecting facilities to determine any work that needs to be completed.Maintaining a maintenance checklist of any tasks that need to be accomplished daily while assisting staff to ensure that all tasks are being completed efficiently.Assigning staff to specific tasks, carefully inspecting the work upon completion to ensure the job is up to standard.Following up on and managing any customer complaints.Training new employees, preparing performance reviews and handling disciplinary action when necessary.Fully understand how to use tools and equipment that are needed for the job, such as carpet cleaners, power washers, buffers etc.Continue to ensure that safety is the highest priority, ensuring staff fully comprehend the tasks and that they are using the proper safety equipment.Qualifications &amp; Experience Required:Proven supervisory experience within janitorial / facility management.Proven experience managing a large and diverse team.Bilingual (English and Spanish)Strong Microsoft Office skills including Word and Excel.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Facilities Manager , Property & Facilities Management - Regional Facilities Manger
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>786</id>
        <date>2019-11-22 18:45:20</date>
        <title>M&E and RHVAC Director</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=786&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Jacksonville, Florida</location>
        <description>
            Job Title: M&amp;E and RHVAC DirectorLocation: Jacksonville, FloridaSalary: $140,000 to $150,000 + bonus, full benefits packageStart Date: ASAPJob Type: Direct Hire, Permanent Resourcing Group is working in partnership with a contractor who is looking to hire for the position Mechanical &amp; Electrical and Refrigeration / HVAC Director.The Director is responsible for leading a multi-state team across all States of operation, and provides service excellence to the company's clients for this area of the business. This involves managing all aspects of the mechanical, electrical, refrigeration and HVAC team's services to meet required service levels, and all other KPI's as set by the business. Delivering prescribed maintenance services including project works within budget is a fundamental element of the role. Main ResponsibilitiesDeliver an overall M&amp;E and RHVAC service within budget while meeting all required service levels of KPI's.Responsible for training, up-skilling the senior management team across M&amp;E and RHVACEnsure all operational areas operate within a safe workplace and adhere to company health and safety policies and procedures as well as meeting stated aims and KPIs.Serves as subject matter expert for all technical services provided.Responsible for creating the technical framework that outlines ways of working for the multi-state technicians.Creation of annual technical training plans and to prepare and present monthly statue pack reportsMonitor and report on KPIs monthlyProactively identify performance issues and provide immediate feedbackDeliver an overall multi-skilled services within budget and meeting all required service levels and KPI'sDesigns and creates apprenticeship program.Monitor the delivery of reactive, proactive electromechanical, planned maintenance, ensuring completion against KPIsDelivering prescribed maintenance services including project works within budget is a fundamental element of the roleLiaise with key suppliers to ensure that parts supply and subcontracted services are delivered to within acceptable standard, and to budgetManage the performance &amp; relationship of all maintenance vendors and budgetsLiaise with all relevant regulatory authorities for licensing and to meet legislation requirementsDrives operational service performance of suppliers inclusive of training and onsite visits.Business Operations:Lead on-going efforts for process improvement to enhance productivity and increase efficiencies while sustaining high level of qualityImplement cost reduction, profit enhancing strategiesDirect and execute new customer/contract start-up operationsContinually assess financial performance of accounts, identify problem areas, implement plan to address concernsFinancially manage and ensure account profit and productivity goals are metIdentify on-going financial and operational efficiencies. ESSENTIAL Skills and ExperienceDemonstrated record of accomplishment in a similar role within facilities managementTrade qualified and relevant licenses, A Grade Electrician, Mechanical, RefrigerationState Licensed10+ years of experience in managing a state services teamExperience with the development and maintenance of budgets, labor costs and monitoring financial information.Advanced level of use and understanding of Microsoft Office (Excel and Word).Strong customer service focus is required.Strong interpersonal skills; able to effectively influence others through positive, proactive communication style;Excellent written and oral communication skills and sound problem-solving and decision making capabilities.Adept at dealing with all levels of management, possessing strong consultative and communication skills; Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Property & Facilities Management - Director </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>784</id>
        <date>2019-11-20 23:21:52</date>
        <title>Senior Superintendent - Commerical Interiors</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=784&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            My client is a New York based privately held General Contracting and Construction Management company experienced and knowledgeable in all areas of the building and construction sector.They focus on interior fit out on commercial projects in Manhattan.Job Description Senior Interior Construction Superintendent will:Become fully versed in the requirements of the contract for the project.Develop, update, modify and maintain the project schedule including a master schedule, 30-day look ahead schedule, 2-week look ahead schedule, Executive Summary schedule, critical path schedule and schedule narrative.Assure that daily safety walk thru's are conducted and documented and that all information arising out of the walk thru's are distributed to the appropriate subcontractor foreman to correct safety deficiencies.Develop, maintain and update as required the site safety and logistics plans.Train and develop the skills of all direct reports.Conduct weekly foreman and superintendents' meetings. Assure that regular meeting minutes are taken and distributed to all parties in attendance. Include a "Ball in Court" column to ensure that items/issues are being addressed and completed. Assure that work progress, safety, material storage and lay down areas, job cleanliness, etc. are discussed and appropriate actions taken to ensure a safe and productive site.Assure that daily construction reports (DCR's) are prepared daily and that they are thorough, descriptive and accurate.Assure that substantive daily progress photos are taken daily and that they clearly depict the progress of the project. These photos should be inManage both subcontractor and direct labor to ensure that the work flow is productive and safe.Attend weekly meetings with the project team for the following purposes: 1) update the team on the status of the fieldwork and schedule; 2) communicate any issues that require the input or action of others on the project team that has an impact on the project; 3) proactively communicate both good and bad news to the team so that the proper business decisions can be made; 4) be prepared to provide solutions to any issues that arise in the field during the course of the workEstablish and maintain a system of document control to assure that work is being installed in accordance with the latest design documents and approved shop drawings.Ensure that field issues that require additional information are communicated timely to the project manager so that RFI's can be issued immediately to the design team.Assure the required job permits and approvals from jurisdictional agencies are secured, posted and renewed prior and during the course of the project. The Successful Applicant Interior Construction Superintendent will: MUST have an active New York City Construction Superintendent Experience 5-10 years experience as a Construction Superintendent. Proven project list of $10M+ projects in New York City Proficient with software such as Microsoft Office (Excel, Word, Powerpoint). Bachelor's degree in Construction or equivalent work experience is preferred.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Superintendent </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>783</id>
        <date>2019-11-19 23:36:52</date>
        <title>Senior Cost Manager - New York - $160k</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=783&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            Senior Cost Manager - New York - $160k My client, a global leader in project and cost consulting, providing clients with owner's representative expertise and advice throughout the life cycle of their construction projects. The project is a major refurbishment scheme worth over $450m over a 24 month period. This project is a flagship project within NY and working alongside a high profile investment company.A Bachelor's Degree or its equivalent in Construction Management or Related Field is required by the client, plus 3 years minimum experience as a Senior Cost Manager with a consultancy. Key Task: Advising client on strategies, managing prequalification of vendors, assessing proposals, bids, and bid leveling documents, making final recommendations to the client, attending &amp; chairing bid interviews, and managing appointment process.Manage estimating services for full project by developing project estimates (relating to construction, fees, direct work and other costs), reviewing estimations prepared by junior team members, presenting estimates to client, presenting value engineering recommendations and risk assessments to client, meeting with vendors to review, validate, and challenge costs, and reviewing estimates by utilizing benchmark data collected from other projects.Manage cost reporting by establishing reporting schedule, reviewing &amp; presenting cost reports and forecasts, reviewing project budget &amp; spend forecast with the client, developing &amp; maintaining commercial risk register, and hosting periodic meetings with project team &amp; vendors.Manage cost control process by reviewing payment application assessments prepared by junior team members, liaising with project managers to recommend contractor entitlements, reviewing requests for change orders from vendors &amp; making recommendations to client, and using dispute prevention/management/resolution procedures to manage payment requisitions, change orders, and contractual disputes.Salary: Ranges from $140k - $150k depending on experience, plus benefits. If you would like to apply for this position, please email your resume to ian.crosby@resourcinggroup.us or call on 646 515 1796.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Cost Manager</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>782</id>
        <date>2019-11-19 23:16:59</date>
        <title>Estimator - Manhattan - $150k</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=782&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            Estimator - Manhattan - $150kI am currently working with a long standing, leading New York ground up contractor who have been established 35 years. Due to work load and multiple project wins they are looking for a Estimator, as they expand there team. The work is predominately working within the residential affordable housing sector.This is a excellent opportunity to fast track your career. But you will be joining an established business, with a very healthy order book already in place. A leader in the mixed-income, affordable, supportive and institutional housing sectors and as a partner of the New York City and State housing agencies. This is a fantastic opportunity for any Estimator to forward there career, and work for a people friendly company with excellent benefits.Salary Range from - $150k (Experience Depending)If you would like to apply for this position, please email your resume to ian.crosby@resourcinggroup.us or call 646 515 1796 to discuss in more detail.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Estimator</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>781</id>
        <date>2019-11-19 23:11:32</date>
        <title>Construction Estimator - Boston - $120k</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=781&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Boston, Massachusetts</location>
        <description>
            Construction Estimator - Boston - $120k I am currently working with a established Boston GC, who are looking to hire a up and coming Estimator who is interested in joining a company with fast-track career progression. Due to work load and multiple project wins they are looking add a Estimator to their team. This hire will not only be an integral part of the company, but they will need to have the ambition to help grow the Estimating team and in the future be the lead company Estimator for the Boston office. The work is predominately working within ground up construction, covering a number of sectors including, high end, beach side multi-family Cape Cod, and Boston Homes, Commercial Office, institutional &amp; Commercial, and Multi-Family. Projects will range in value from $5m to $50m. This is a fantastic opportunity for any Estimator looking to forward there career, and work for a people friendly company with excellent benefits. Salary Range from - $100k - $120k (Experience Depending) , 401, health care, bonus. Please could we set up a call to discuss the company in more detail, or to apply, please email your resume to ian.crosby@resourcinggroup.us or call 646 515 1796 to discuss the position.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Estimator</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>780</id>
        <date>2019-11-19 23:10:50</date>
        <title>Superintendent - Ground Up</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=780&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>New Jersey, New York</location>
        <description>
            Superintendent required for a ground up project based in New Jersey - Primary role is to provide overall field management and administration to field employees, subcontractors, vendors and suppliers. You may be required to manage a major project or many smaller projects simultaneously.Ideal candidate will have previous experience working on ground up residential projects and warehouse build outsCore ResponsibilitiesDeliver a quality project safely, on time, within budget and with focus on establishing positive relationshipsManage subcontractors and vendors in a coordinated manner.Provide input and valuable review of subcontractor scope to assist the PMEnsure that Quality Control requirements are met and followed in accordance with the Contract DocumentsProvide assistance with pre-job planning, strategizing and conceptual schedulingProduce tight, realistic construction schedulesEnsure that no subcontractor is allowed to work on-site without an approved Insurance certificate, signed Subcontract or a Letter of IntentProduce daily reports and Weekly Status Reports and assist the project team in developing monthly cost reportsTake digital progress photographsEstablish good working relationships with government agenciesQualificationsBS or BA in engineering or related discipline. (A proven track record of Construction and/or Management experience in the field may be substituted for degree.)Thorough knowledge of Safety Risk Management process, including understanding of EMR, IR, SR, FR and how to effectively improve Safety performance ratings in each of these areasThorough knowledge of confined space, hazmat, asbestos, lead paint and other hazard policies and proceduresSuccessfully completed OSHA 30-hour safety trainingResourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Superintendent </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>779</id>
        <date>2019-11-19 23:08:06</date>
        <title>Commercial Building Engineer</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=779&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            Building EngineerManhattanUp to $130,000 Resourcing Group is working with one of the largest and longest operating hedge funds in the industry. A company who allocates capital across more than 200 entrepreneurial portfolio managers that invest in a diverse set of strategies. With more than 2,500 employees, our client harnesses the entrepreneurial drive of their staff.We seek to attract, develop and retain the best talent in the industry, offering an opportunity to develop your career by working with a leadership team that has years of industry experience across a variety of disciplines.We encourage staff to work together in a collegial and collaborative team-based environment. This enables the business to continuously improve day-to-day activities, and ultimately the firm as a whole. The Building Engineer will assist engineering management of the mechanical and electrical systems, perform general maintenance and repairs, as well as provide a safe, efficient and comfortable working environment for staff throughout the Firm's locations. The Engineer will need to be hands-on and work closely with building management, IT and Facilities staff. Responsibilities include;Perform basic facilities maintenance and repairs. Including Critical Facility Systems (i.e., Office HVAC, CRAC, Dry Cooler, UPS, STS, ATS, Emergency Generator)Monitor and respond to environmental alarms (not limited to normal business hours)Respond to employee requests in a professional and timely mannerAssist Engineering team in managing the installation and maintenance of the architectural, mechanical and electrical systemsSupervise vendors during preventive maintenance and execute corrective measure as requiredCoordinate procedures with landlord staff of any integrated systemsPlan, coordinate and execute renovation projects Qualifications &amp; Skills Required;5+ years of relevant engineering experienceCompletion of accredited refrigeration training programNYC FDNY Refrigeration Machine Operator License (Q-01 or Q-99)EPA 608 Universal CertificateMust have demonstrated customer service and strong organizational skillsAbility to multi-task, be hands on and prioritize in fast paced/demanding environmentQuick learner, detail oriented; demonstrable thoroughness and strong ownership of workGood team player with a strong willingness to participate and help othersAbility to prioritize in a fast moving, high pressure, constantly changing environment; High sense of urgencyCapable of working flexible hours including nights and weekends when requiredCapable to travel to satellite offices located in the U.S.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Maintenance Technician/Handyman , Property & Facilities Management - Chief Engineer, Property & Facilities Management - Building Engineer
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>778</id>
        <date>2019-11-19 23:01:08</date>
        <title>Senior Superintendent - Commerical Interiors</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=778&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            My client is a New York based privately held General Contracting and Construction Management company experienced and knowledgeable in all areas of the building and construction sector. They focus on interior fit out on commercial projects in Manhattan. Job Description Senior Interior Construction Superintendent will: Become fully versed in the requirements of the contract for the project.Develop, update, modify and maintain the project schedule including a master schedule, 30-day look ahead schedule, 2-week look ahead schedule, Executive Summary schedule, critical path schedule and schedule narrative.Assure that daily safety walk thru's are conducted and documented and that all information arising out of the walk thru's are distributed to the appropriate subcontractor foreman to correct safety deficiencies.Develop, maintain and update as required the site safety and logistics plans.Train and develop the skills of all direct reports.Conduct weekly foreman and superintendents' meetings. Assure that regular meeting minutes are taken and distributed to all parties in attendance. Include a "Ball in Court" column to ensure that items/issues are being addressed and completed. Assure that work progress, safety, material storage and lay down areas, job cleanliness, etc. are discussed and appropriate actions taken to ensure a safe and productive site.Assure that daily construction reports (DCR's) are prepared daily and that they are thorough, descriptive and accurate.Assure that substantive daily progress photos are taken daily and that they clearly depict the progress of the project. These photos should be inManage both subcontractor and direct labor to ensure that the work flow is productive and safe.Attend weekly meetings with the project team for the following purposes: 1) update the team on the status of the fieldwork and schedule; 2) communicate any issues that require the input or action of others on the project team that has an impact on the project; 3) proactively communicate both good and bad news to the team so that the proper business decisions can be made; 4) be prepared to provide solutions to any issues that arise in the field during the course of the workEstablish and maintain a system of document control to assure that work is being installed in accordance with the latest design documents and approved shop drawings.Ensure that field issues that require additional information are communicated timely to the project manager so that RFI's can be issued immediately to the design team.Assure the required job permits and approvals from jurisdictional agencies are secured, posted and renewed prior and during the course of the project. The Successful Applicant Interior Construction Superintendent will: MUST have an active New York City Construction Superintendent Experience 5-10 years experience as a Construction Superintendent. Proven project list of $10M+ projects in New York City Proficient with software such as Microsoft Office (Excel, Word, Powerpoint). Bachelor's degree in Construction or equivalent work experience is preferred.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Superintendent </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>777</id>
        <date>2019-11-15 21:45:50</date>
        <title>Commercial Building Engineer</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=777&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            Commercial Building EngineerManhattan Resourcing Group is working with a global investment management firm that manages over $25 billion in assets, with thousands of employees working across offices in the United States, Europe and Asia. We are recruiting a Building Engineer to work within a Class A, high rise building in the heart of Manhattan.The Building Engineer is responsible to ensuring the efficient operation and maintenance of mechanical, electrical and plumbing equipment and systems within the building. You will be expected to maintain a safe and clean working environment, conducting routine assessments, manage the performance of day-to-day preventive and corrective maintenance for assigned property. Key Responsibilities;Perform all plumbing, electrical, or HVAC requirements of the building.Maintain heating equipment, chillers (air and/ or water cooled), DX units, pumps, cooling towers, fan coil units, VAV, and air distribution systems, etc.Monitor and adjust all mechanical/pneumatic equipment, steam stations, control gauges, distributor panels, valves, thermostats, diffusers, and other equipment necessary to provide a comfortable environment for the buildings.Monitor Energy Management.Repair doors, ceilings, floors and other general repairs, adjustments and installations within the facility.Perform preventive maintenance duties in accordance with C&amp;W standards, building protocol and industry best practices, including changing filters, cleaning coils, flushing condensers, greasing fan, pump and motor bearings, inspecting and adjusting belts, monitor condenser, chilled, heating and secondary water chemical treatment and its associated feed equipment, clean and maintain cooling towers, and perform annual inspections/ scheduled routines as directed.Inspect engine room equipment, fan room equipment, cooling tower, all motors, house pumps, electric rooms, back-up generator, fire pump(s), sump pump(s), and ejector pumps. Replace lamps, light fixtures, reinstall or replace signage, verify rooms are clean and clear of obstructions and debris.Perform additional fire and life safety inspections as per NFPA and local jurisdiction, C&amp;W standards, building protocol and as directed.Document and report activities.Respond immediately to emergency situations (fire, evacuation, equipment failure, etc.Comply with all applicable codes, regulations, governmental agency, and company directives as relates to building operations and practice safe work habits. Experience &amp; Qualifications;High School Diploma of GED Equivalent.Proven experience in operating mechanical, electrical and plumbing systems in a commercial setting.Appropriate license/permit for trade i.e. Journeyman or Master Electrician License or City Licenses such as Refrigeration Certificate of Fitness, High Pressure Boiler License, High Pressure Steam Operator, etc.).Thorough knowledge in all building systems operations, maintenance and repair.Experience in operation, maintenance and basic repair of HVAC, boilers, heaters, pumps, refrigerant systems, compressors, water systems, etc.Knowledge of energy management systems, techniques and operations.Basic Computing Skills in Outlook, Excel &amp; Word.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Maintenance/Engineering Manager , Property & Facilities Management - Chief Engineer, Property & Facilities Management - Building Engineer
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>776</id>
        <date>2019-11-15 00:27:55</date>
        <title>Facilities Coordinator</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=776&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>50,001 – 75,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Illinois, Illinois</location>
        <description>
            Job Title: Facilities CoordinatorLocation: Downers Grove, IllinoisSalary: $50,000 to $55,000 plus full benefits packageStart Date: December 2019, ASAPJob Type: Direct Hire Resourcing Group is working in partnership with a Global Facilities Management provider who is looking to hire for the position Facilities Coordinator.The successful canddiate will manage vendors to ensure that exemplary facilities management services are provided to the Client.Main Responsibilities Oversite of internal and external service delivery teams, ensuring quality of services provided are continually improved and exceed customer expectations.Maintain a safe, clean and comfortable working environment. Onsite interface between general contractors and subcontractors for special projects as related to building operations.Coordinate assigned vendor activities, ensure delivery of services and value for money is achieved through robust management of suppliers and measurement of performance as outlined in service agreements / contracts.Minimize risk and maintain or improve profitability against agreed targets. Ensure KPIs, business, and financial targets are meet and all required reporting is completed as required by the due date.Identify and pursue opportunities; keep abreast of best practice within the industry by maintaining contact with peers in other market sectors.Compliance with all applicable legislation, client processes, and life / safety and security procedures.Manage and maintain positive relationships with clients, suppliers and team members; share knowledge with the Facilities teams across all sites; maintain high levels of customer service at all times. Provide strategic and technical support and general advice to clients, peers, and teams.Oversight and support for client for moves, restacks, projects, and buildouts.Assist with coordination and oversight of preventative maintenance and repair and maintenance on critical equipment, and monitoring/responding to equipment alarms.Ability to work nights and weekends as needed; available on-call during scheduled rotations.Management of client's ISO 14001 accreditation and programs. Ensure maintenance of certification, including document control/management, auditing, Green Team, utility/usage data entry, legislative monitoring and compliance, annual reporting, etc.Responsible for first responder/floor warden team, including recruitment and coordination of training.Conduct ergonomic workstation assessments, create reports and maintain documentation, and issue ergonomic equipment.Risk assessments of on-site operations and mechanical areas; maintenance of the site's risk register.FM site and safety inspections, recording results and ensuring close out of non-conformances.Oversee/conduct audits relating to ISO 14001, contractors, site operations, HSE and security.Liaise and maintain positive relationships with client property management company and management vendors.Oversight of day porter activities. Monthly janitorial inspections, including walkthroughs with building management and janitorial vendors, and follow up on open items.Special projects as needed / required by the client or FM. ESSENTIAL Skills and Experience3 years minimum experience in a similar role within Facilities Management5 years' experience working in an Office Services, Facilities ManagementFMP or CFM certification, or any recognized HSE qualificationsHigh School Diploma To apply for this post, please respond to this advert by sending us your most up to date resume in word format or contact Jayde Edgley on 646 846 6634. Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Facilities Co-ordinator
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>775</id>
        <date>2019-11-15 00:03:29</date>
        <title>Assistant Project Manager - Construction</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=775&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Brooklyn, New York</location>
        <description>
            We are seeking an Assistant Project Manager - Construction to join our client's team fast growing team! You will oversee project planning, scheduling, budgeting, and implementation. General Contractor based in Brooklyn who is working on affordable housing projects.Responsibilities * Oversee all aspects of construction project from planning to implementation for commercial construction projects that are larger (10+) million. * Assist with Submittals and change orders * Allocate resources for assigned projects * Supervise onsite personnel and subcontractors * Interface with project inspectors, contractors, architects, engineers, city and county officials, and clients * Negotiate with contractors to receive reasonable order costs * Maintain high standards of workmanship that adhere to original plans and specifications Qualifications * Previous experience in construction management for a GC or developer * Familiarity with construction management software * 2 to 10 years experience and experience with commercial new build projects* College degree in Construction strongly preferred Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Assistant Project Manager</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>773</id>
        <date>2019-11-13 16:27:06</date>
        <title>Interior Construction Superintendent</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=773&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Brooklyn, New York</location>
        <description>
            My client is a New York based privately held General Contracting and Construction Management company experienced and knowledgeable in all areas of the building and construction sector. They focus in high-end residential projects in NYC, Brooklyn and Queens. Job Description Interior Construction Superintendent will:Verify accuracy of construction plan measurements of floors, walls, ceilings, etc. and identify discrepancies and take corrective action with Estimating or Project Manager. Handling projects that are from the ground up. Enforce safety policies and procedures. Make active attempts to resolve labor disputes and personnel problems. Take unresolved issues to Project Manager when needed. Schedule and coordinate work crews consistent with project demands and schedule Schedule the routing and delivery of materials taking appropriate precautions to prevent job-site theft, organize building access &amp; elevator usage. Co-chair weekly project team meetings to discuss project status. Document issues that impact the project schedule or will impact project budget and assign resolution to appropriate individuals in attendance. Create a checklist to track and monitor every aspect of pre- construction on a major ground up project such as pre construction survey, all DOB Permits.The Successful Applicant Interior Construction Superintendent will: MUST have an active New York City Construction Superintendent Experience 5-10 years experience as a Construction Superintendent. Proven project list of $150M+ projects in New York CityExperience in ground up work, interior work, commercial, civil. Proficient with software such as Microsoft Office (Excel, Word, Powerpoint). Bachelor's degree in Construction or equivalent work experience is preferred. Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Superintendent </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>772</id>
        <date>2019-11-12 17:48:30</date>
        <title>Chief Maintenance Manager</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=772&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>New Jersey, New York</location>
        <description>
            Chief Maintenance ManagerStaten Island Residential Property Management $85,000 - $120,000 Resourcing Group is working with a successful commercial real estate company based in New York with a high number or properties under their management.Our client's integrated team works closely to create an environment where tenants are happy and employees can flourish. We are looking to recruit an individual who loves what they do, enjoys learning, and wants to be a part of growing company. The Maintenance Manager will be responsible for overseeing the maintenance and repair efforts for an assigned community, including the physical aspects of the property, HVAC, electrical, plumbing, carpentry, major appliances and amenities. They will ensure that all work meets company safety and operating standards and any applicable laws and regulations. You will be required to have 4+ years experience in residential building and apartment maintenance (or related). HVAC experience is also required, as is experience managing both union (32BJ) and non union staff To be considered for this position, please contact your specialist consultant, Matt Allen, at Resourcing Group Recruitment on 646-891-4639 or send your resume to matt.allen@resourcinggroup.usResourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Maintenance Manager
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>770</id>
        <date>2019-11-05 21:43:47</date>
        <title>Superintendent</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=770&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            I am actively recruiting for a Superintendent for a mid-size general contractor based in Manhattan. The role is primarily responsible for day-to-day field planning, staffing and a supervisor on the active job site.Duties and Responsibilities:Management of all site staff.Verify accuracy of drawing plan measurements of floors, walls, ceilings, etc. Identify discrepancies and take corrective Action with Estimating or Project Manager.Assist the Project Manager in planning job schedule to ensure schedule takes into account current tenant work schedules and building access/elevator usage for oversized materials.Schedule with Project Manager weekly project construction meetings with subcontractors, architects, engineers, other vendors and owner to discuss project status.Schedule the routing and delivery of materials and take appropriate precautions to prevent job-site theft.Submit daily reports and document issues that impact the project schedule or will impact project budget and assign resolution to appropriate individuals in attendance.Make active attempts to resolve labor disputes and personnel problems. Take unresolved issues to Project Manager and Director of Operations when needed.Recommend overtime work requests to Project Manager and obtain appropriate security clearances for approved overtime.Establish effective working relationships with client, architects, building manager, building engineer and others.Actively enforce all building regulations regarding noise, use of elevators, security, etc.Ensure outstanding project safety, subcontractor performance, on-time scheduling, specification conformance and quality control (i.e. daily toolbox talks, etc)Obtain client and or architect signature on final punch list completion certificate. Desired Skills and ExperienceMUST have a valid 30 hour OSHA certificateWork experience should include some supervisory responsibility as a General Foreman, Field Engineer or Assistant Superintendent.Bachelor's degree in Construction Science or equivalent work experience (minimum 5 years)Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Superintendent </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>768</id>
        <date>2019-11-01 20:48:46</date>
        <title>Senior Project Manager - Construction Residential</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=768&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Brooklyn, New York</location>
        <description>
            My client is looking for a Senior Project Manager to be a part of their New York City office. They are a large General Contracting firm with offices in New York and New Jersey, specializing in all aspects of Residential, Commercial, Industrial and Institutional Construction. Over the last 25 years they have grown to annual gross of more than $300M.This is an exciting opportunity for an experienced Senior Project Manager with a strong background in high rise residential projects based in the five boroughs.Project DetailsStart Date - Dec/Jan Project Value - $250M Location - Brooklyn Size - 800,000 SF 2 High Rise Residential Towers 30 story &amp; 40 storyDuties and Responsibilities: * Planning and strategy of project development from the design effort through construction, obtaining Certificate of Occupancy and project closeout. * Oversight and coordination of the design development with the design team from schematic design to 100% CDs with development of project scopes of work. * Coordination with expeditors for plan review/approvals with the NYC DOB and permitting of project. * Management and coordination with the selected construction manager/general contractor to keep the project within established schedule and budget constraints. * Cost reporting of the project; tracking consultant contracts and construction schedule of values. * Reporting to the Senior Project Executive.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Project Manager </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>767</id>
        <date>2019-11-01 20:12:54</date>
        <title>Director of Operations</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=767&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Jacksonville, Florida</location>
        <description>
            Job Title: Director of OperationsLocation: Jacksonville, FloridaSalary: $110,000 to $120,000 + bonus and full benefitsStart Date: ASAPJob Type: Direct Hire Resourcing Group is working in partnership with a Facilities Management service provider who is looking to hire for the position Head of Operations. You will be responsible for price negotiations with a multi-million dollar maintenance budget. You will oversee all commercial matters for the company including procurement strategy, contracts, cost, related systems, process and reporting cycles. Delivering the prescribed services within budget is a fundamental element of the role Main Responsibilities Provide commercial and contractual management support and advice as requiredProvide commercial and legal advice for contractual claims, documents, negotiations, arrangements and compliance policies as required.Lead face to face negotiations with existing and potential major suppliers to ensure best value provision of maintenance services.Monitor and assess the standard of commercial dealings, and support the implementation or measures to ensure continuous improvement to manage the commercial risk, comply with guidelines and regulations, and deliver improved outcomes.Establish good working relationships with the businesses maintenance teams to optimise the commercial success of maintenance activities.Create rate card database for maintenance providers and utilise national purchasing values. Seek, develop and deliver opportunities for commercial and procurement improvements across the business Business OperationsPrepare and review plans, forecasts and budgets, and manage planned outcomes within approved budgets, financial plans and funding arrangements at all times.Drive continuous improvement - especially in service levels and costsEstablish KPIs and KPI programs, prepare for and chair contractor review sessions with State maintenance leads.Manage contractor complianceDevelop and maintain strategic relationships with key suppliers to ensure that services are ordered and delivered within designated timeframesLiaise and negotiate with suppliers where services have not been delivered to scope/specification and/or to achieve cost savings across the business.Analyse expenditure, supplier arrangements and procurement practices to identify areas where significant benefit can be achievedAnalyse supplier base to determine scope for consolidationConduct regular reviews with key suppliers to ensure contracted benefits are realised and identify additional improvement opportunities to further reduce costs and improve quality of service. ESSENTIAL Skills and Experience5 years record of accomplishment in a similar role with a facilities management firmA degree in finance or commerce or similarDemonstrated commercial negotiation experienceExperience with the development and maintenance of budgets, labor costs and monitoring financial information.Experience conducting high quality face to face commercial negotiations for multimillion dollar (maintenance contracts)Advanced level of use and understanding of Microsoft Office (Excel and Word). To apply for this post, please respond to this advert by sending us your most up to date resume in word format or contact Jayde Edgley on 646 595 74 64 Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Property & Facilities Management - Director </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>766</id>
        <date>2019-11-01 19:49:47</date>
        <title>Chief Maintenance Manager</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=766&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>New Jersey, New York</location>
        <description>
            Chief Maintenance ManagerStaten Island Residential Property Management $85,000 - $120,000 Resourcing Group is working with a successful commercial real estate company based in New York with a high number or properties under their management.Our client's integrated team works closely to create an environment where tenants are happy and employees can flourish. We are looking to recruit an individual who loves what they do, enjoys learning, and wants to be a part of growing company. The Maintenance Manager will be responsible for overseeing the maintenance and repair efforts for an assigned community, including the physical aspects of the property, HVAC, electrical, plumbing, carpentry, major appliances and amenities. They will ensure that all work meets company safety and operating standards and any applicable laws and regulations. You will be required to have 4+ years experience in residential building and apartment maintenance (or related). HVAC experience is also required, as is experience managing both union (32BJ) and non union staff To be considered for this position, please contact your specialist consultant, Matt Allen, at Resourcing Group Recruitment on 646-891-4639 or send your resume to matt.allen@resourcinggroup.usResourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Maintenance Manager
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>765</id>
        <date>2019-11-01 14:26:52</date>
        <title>Head of Commercials and Facilities Management</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=765&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Jacksonville, Florida</location>
        <description>
            Job Title: Head of Commercials and Facilities ManagementLocation: Jacksonville, FloridaSalary: $110,000 to $120,000 + bonus and full benefitsStart Date: ASAPJob Type: Direct Hire Resourcing Group is working in partnership with a Facilities Management service provider who is looking to hire for the position Head of Commercials. You will be responsible for price negotiations with a multi-million dollar maintenance budget. You will oversee all commercial matters for the company including procurement strategy, contracts, cost, related systems, process and reporting cycles. Delivering the prescribed services within budget is a fundamental element of the role Main Responsibilities Provide commercial and contractual management support and advice as requiredProvide commercial and legal advice for contractual claims, documents, negotiations, arrangements and compliance policies as required.Lead face to face negotiations with existing and potential major suppliers to ensure best value provision of maintenance services.Monitor and assess the standard of commercial dealings, and support the implementation or measures to ensure continuous improvement to manage the commercial risk, comply with guidelines and regulations, and deliver improved outcomes.Establish good working relationships with the businesses maintenance teams to optimise the commercial success of maintenance activities.Create rate card database for maintenance providers and utilise national purchasing values. Seek, develop and deliver opportunities for commercial and procurement improvements across the business Business OperationsPrepare and review plans, forecasts and budgets, and manage planned outcomes within approved budgets, financial plans and funding arrangements at all times.Drive continuous improvement - especially in service levels and costsEstablish KPIs and KPI programs, prepare for and chair contractor review sessions with State maintenance leads.Manage contractor complianceDevelop and maintain strategic relationships with key suppliers to ensure that services are ordered and delivered within designated timeframesLiaise and negotiate with suppliers where services have not been delivered to scope/specification and/or to achieve cost savings across the business.Analyse expenditure, supplier arrangements and procurement practices to identify areas where significant benefit can be achievedAnalyse supplier base to determine scope for consolidationConduct regular reviews with key suppliers to ensure contracted benefits are realised and identify additional improvement opportunities to further reduce costs and improve quality of service. ESSENTIAL Skills and Experience5 years record of accomplishment in a similar role with a facilities management firmA degree in finance or commerce or similarDemonstrated commercial negotiation experienceExperience with the development and maintenance of budgets, labor costs and monitoring financial information.Experience conducting high quality face to face commercial negotiations for multimillion dollar (maintenance contracts)Advanced level of use and understanding of Microsoft Office (Excel and Word). To apply for this post, please respond to this advert by sending us your most up to date resume in word format or contact Jayde Edgley on 646 595 74 64 Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Property & Facilities Management - Director </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>764</id>
        <date>2019-11-01 14:10:18</date>
        <title>Regional Manager of Multi-Skilled Technicians</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=764&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Jacksonville, Florida</location>
        <description>
            Job Title: Regional Manager of Multi-Skilled TechniciansLocation: Jacksonville, FloridaSalary: $90,000 to $100,000 + bonus, full benefits packageStart Date: ASAPJob Type: Direct Hire Resourcing Group is working in partnership with a Facilities Management service provider who is looking to hire for the position Regional Manager of Multi-Skilled Technicians. You will be responsible for managing the service delivery of multi-skilled technicians involving Electrical and Mechanical services for multiple retail stores. Main ResponsibilitiesResponsible for training, up-skilling the mechanical and electrical techniciansPrepare and present monthly statue pack reportsMonitor and report on KPIs monthlyProactively identify performance issues and provide immediate feedbackDeliver an overall multi-skilled services within budget and meeting all required service levels and KPI'sMonitor the delivery of reactive, proactive electromechanical, planned maintenance, ensuring completion against KPIsDelivering prescribed maintenance services including project works within budget is a fundamental element of the roleLiaise with key suppliers to ensure that parts supply and subcontracted services are delivered to within acceptable standard, and to budgetManage the performance &amp; relationship of all maintenance vendors and budgetsLiaise with all relevant regulatory authorities for licensing and to meet legislation requirementsDrives operational service performance of suppliers inclusive of training and onsite visits.Business Operations:Lead on-going efforts for process improvement to enhance productivity and increase efficiencies while sustaining high level of qualityImplement cost reduction, profit enhancing strategiesDirect and execute new customer/contract start-up operationsContinually assess financial performance of accounts, identify problem areas, implement plan to address concernsFinancially manage and ensure account profit and productivity goals are metIdentify on-going financial and operational efficiencies. ESSENTIAL Skills and ExperienceDemonstrated record of accomplishment in a similar role within facilities managementTrade qualified and relevant licenses, A Grade ElectricianState Licensed8+ years of experience in managing a nationwide state multi-skilled teamExperience with the development and maintenance of budgets, labor costs and monitoring financial information.Advanced level of use and understanding of Microsoft Office (Excel and Word).Strong customer service focus is required.Strong interpersonal skills; able to effectively influence others through positive, proactive communication style;Excellent written and oral communication skills and sound problem-solving and decision making capabilities.Adept at dealing with all levels of management, possessing strong consultative and communication skills; Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Property & Facilities Management - Director </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>763</id>
        <date>2019-11-01 13:19:06</date>
        <title>Director of Operations and Facilities Management</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=763&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Newark, New Jersey</location>
        <description>
            Job Title: Director of Operations Location: New Jersey Salary: $135,000 plus Bonus Travel: 15% Essential Duties You will be responsible for the day to day management of all east coast contractsEnsure all sites operate within budget and analyse their financial performancesAt all times, provide quality service to the client and meet the organizations business objectivesCreate lead generations through sales development and negotiate contract pricingOversee and direct new contract mobilization and their complianceMeet and develop client relationships and expand current contractsDevelop and coach the management team within the region and manage staff performanceCreate and distribute reports on region activity and deliver presentations to senior executivesReview legal contracts and ensure accounts are adhering to company policies Essential Requirements Minimum 10 years Facilities Management experienceMust have managed FM service provider contracts previously such as janitorial, waste, engineering, electrical, security, sustainability and energyMust have worked in similar roles serving the needs of commercial buildings, airports, prisons, education, retail, data centers and financial institutions5 years experience managing budgets, P&amp;Ls at least $20M of annual revenueBe able to travel for business when needed 15% of your time (DL Essential)Bachelor's degreeOSHA 30 CertificationPrior union negotiation experience with IUOE and service tradesWorking knowledge of industry leading CMMS programs We are working with a Global FM service provider who is looking to hire a Director of Operations to manage their facilities management contracts in the East Coast. The successful person will be a natural business leader who has the ability to lead and motivate others. You are a detail orientated individual who is persuasive, clear and concise with a proven track record within facilities management. In return, you will be rewarded with fantastic benefits, a highly competitive bonus scheme and salary. You will be apart of an award winning and market leading firm who continues to expand into new areas and industries each year.To apply for this post, please respond to this advert by sending us your most up to date resume or contact Jayde Edgley on 646 846 6634 or 646 595 7464. Why work with Resourcing Group?* We provide opportunities internationally - jobs where you want, when you need them* Award winning candidate care* Specialist consultants that are experts within their fieldResourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Property & Facilities Management - Director </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>762</id>
        <date>2019-11-01 00:06:04</date>
        <title>Facilities Coordinator</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=762&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>50,001 – 75,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            Job Title: Facilities CoordinatorLocation: Manhattan, NYCSalary: Competitive salary plus full benefits packageStart Date: November 2019, ASAPJob Type: Direct Hire Resourcing Group is working in partnership with a Global Facilities Management provider who is looking to hire for the position Facilities Coordinator. You will effectively manage multiple vendors to ensure that exemplary facilities management services are provided to the Client. Manage resources and promote an ethos of team work and instill a culture of continuous improvement.Offer support and guidance to ensure that workflow is delivered effectively and safely and develop team so they achieve their full potential. Develop a relationship built on trust with the Client in addition to contributing to the development and by supporting the management team through business development and operational activities. Main Responsibilities Oversite of internal and external service delivery teams, ensuring quality of services provided are continually improved and exceed customer expectations.Onsite interface between general contractors and subcontractors for special projects as related to building operations.Coordinate assigned vendor activities, ensure delivery of services and value for money is achieved through robust management of suppliers and measurement of performance as outlined in service agreements / contracts.Ensure KPIs, business, and financial targets are met and all required reporting is completed as required by the due date.Compliance with all applicable legislation and life / safety and security procedures.Oversight and support for client for moves, restacks, projects, and buildouts.Assist with coordination and oversight of preventative maintenance and repair and maintenance on critical equipment, and monitoring/responding to equipment alarms.Ability to work nights and weekends as needed; available on-call during scheduled rotations.Management of client's ISO 14001 accreditation and programs. Ensure maintenance of certification, including document control/management, auditing, Green Team, utility/usage data entry, legislative monitoring and compliance, annual reporting, etc.Responsible for first responder/floor warden team, including recruitment and coordination of training.Conduct ergonomic workstation assessments, create reports and maintain documentation, and issue ergonomic equipment.Risk assessments of on-site operations and mechanical areas; maintenance of the site's risk register.FM site and safety inspections, recording results and ensuring close out of non-conformances.Oversee/conduct audits relating to ISO 14001, contractors, site operations, HSE and security.Liaise and maintain positive relationships with client property management company and management vendors.Oversight of day porter activities. Monthly janitorial inspections, including walkthroughs with building management and janitorial vendors, and follow up on open items. ESSENTIAL Skills and Experience3 years minimum experience in a similar role within Facilities Management5 years' experience working in an Office Services, Facilities ManagementFMP or CFM certification, or any recognized HSE qualificationsHigh School Diploma To apply for this post, please respond to this advert by sending us your most up to date resume in word format or contact Jayde Edgley on 646 846 6634. Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Facilities Co-ordinator
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>761</id>
        <date>2019-10-31 23:57:40</date>
        <title>Facilities Assistant</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=761&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>50,001 – 75,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            Job Title: Facilities AssistantLocation: Manhattan, NYCSalary: Competitive salary plus full benefits packageStart Date: November 2019, ASAPJob Type: Direct Hire Resourcing Group is working in partnership with a Global Facilities Management provider who is looking to hire for the position Facilities Assistant. You will be responsible for providing administrative support, reception coverage and pantry management in a professional, fast-paced, high-energy office as part of a Facilities Management department. This is a customer facing role, where strong customer service skills, organizational skills, and team orientation is required. Main ResponsibilitiesManage the procurement, stocking and issuance of office supplies.Space Management: Coordinate/plan moves of up to 15 people, workstation assignment/management for incoming and outgoing employees, update floor plans, and oversee setup of hoteling stations.Periodically assist with relocation of boxed or crated employee contents.Maintain data base of contractor certificates of insurance (COI), ensuring all COIs are kept current and include appropriate insurance levels.Oversight of all break rooms, pantries and beverage centers: ensure vendors stock pantry areas with consumables to specifications and pantry equipment is cleaned, PM'd and repaired as scheduled/needed.Assistance with management of critical equipment, including monitoring equipment via daily rounds and completion of checklist.Perform periodic checks of all first aid equipment and supplies, and restock supplies as needed.Coordinate with vendors as appropriate or directed by FM for repair and/or maintenance of equipment, furniture, fixtures, and finishes.Support and contribute to the client's environmental accreditation, processes, and programs.Primary back-up for front desk coverage; relieve Receptionist for breaks and lunch, and provide additional coverage as needed. Includes answering calls, registration of guests, issuance of access cards, and induction of vendors.Secondary back-up for Events conference room setup; assist as needed with moving/setup of furniture. ESSENTIAL Skills and ExperiencePrevious experience in a similar role Facilities Management organisationHigh School Graduate5 years facilities management experience To apply for this post, please respond to this advert by sending us your most up to date resume in word format or contact Jayde Edgley on 646 846 6634. Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Facilities Co-ordinator
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>760</id>
        <date>2019-10-31 16:01:54</date>
        <title>Regional HVAC and Refrigeration Director</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=760&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Orlando, Florida</location>
        <description>
            Job Title: Regional HVAC and Refrigeration DirectorLocation: FloridaSalary: Competitive Salary plus full benefits packageStart Date: 2019 / ASAPJob Type: Direct Hire Resourcing Group is working in partnership with a Refrigeration contractor who is looking to hire for the position Regional Refrigeration Director. The successful candidate will be responsible for managing the service delivery of technical trade services involving Refrigeration and HVAC for commercial sites. Main Responsibilities Responsible for training, up-skilling the Refrigeration/HVAC workforce.Prepare and present monthly pack reportsMonitor and report on KPIs monthlyProactively identify performance issues and provide immediate feedbackDeliver an overall Refrigeration &amp; HVAC Services within budget and meeting all required service levels and KPI'sMonitor the delivery of Refrigeration and HVAC planned maintenance, ensuring completion against KPIsManage the performance &amp; relationship of all maintenance vendors and budgetsDevelop and implement a refrigeration gas monitoring system, driving reduction on refrigerant gas usageLiaise with all relevant regulatory authorities for licensing and to meet legislation requirementsDrives operational service performance of suppliers inclusive of training and onsite visits.Business Operations:Lead on-going efforts for process improvement to enhance productivity and increase efficiencies while sustaining high level of qualityDirect and execute new customer/contract start-up operationsContinually assess financial performance of accounts, identify problem areas, implement plan to address concernsFinancially manage and ensure account profit and productivity goals are metIdentify on-going financial and operational efficiencies.ESSENTIAL Skills and ExperienceDemonstrated record of accomplishment in a similar role within facilities managementTrade qualified and relevant licenses in HVAC &amp; Refrigeration8+ years of experience in managing a multi-state trade services teamExperience with the development and maintenance of budgets, labor costs and monitoring financial information.Advanced level of use and understanding of Microsoft Office (Excel and Word).Bachelor's degree in Engineering or similarStrong interpersonal and organization skills required, demonstrating competence in a rapidly changing, growth environment.Strong customer service focus is required.Strong interpersonal skills; able to effectively influence others through positive, proactive communication style;Excellent written and oral communication skills and sound problem-solving and decision making capabilities.Adept at dealing with all levels of management, possessing strong consultative and communication skills; Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Property & Facilities Management - Director </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>759</id>
        <date>2019-10-31 15:59:44</date>
        <title>Regional HVAC and Refrgieration Director</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=759&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Orlando, Florida</location>
        <description>
            Job Title: Regional HVAC and Refrigeration DirectorLocation: FloridaSalary: Competitive Salary plus full benefits packageStart Date: 2019 / ASAPJob Type: Direct Hire Resourcing Group is working in partnership with a Refrigeration contractor who is looking to hire for the position Regional Refrigeration Director. The successful candidate will be responsible for managing the service delivery of technical trade services involving Refrigeration and HVAC for commercial sites. Main Responsibilities Responsible for training, up-skilling the Refrigeration/HVAC workforce.Prepare and present monthly pack reportsMonitor and report on KPIs monthlyProactively identify performance issues and provide immediate feedbackDeliver an overall Refrigeration &amp; HVAC Services within budget and meeting all required service levels and KPI'sMonitor the delivery of Refrigeration and HVAC planned maintenance, ensuring completion against KPIsManage the performance &amp; relationship of all maintenance vendors and budgetsDevelop and implement a refrigeration gas monitoring system, driving reduction on refrigerant gas usageLiaise with all relevant regulatory authorities for licensing and to meet legislation requirementsDrives operational service performance of suppliers inclusive of training and onsite visits.Business Operations:Lead on-going efforts for process improvement to enhance productivity and increase efficiencies while sustaining high level of qualityDirect and execute new customer/contract start-up operationsContinually assess financial performance of accounts, identify problem areas, implement plan to address concernsFinancially manage and ensure account profit and productivity goals are metIdentify on-going financial and operational efficiencies.ESSENTIAL Skills and ExperienceDemonstrated record of accomplishment in a similar role within facilities managementTrade qualified and relevant licenses in HVAC &amp; Refrigeration8+ years of experience in managing a multi-state trade services teamExperience with the development and maintenance of budgets, labor costs and monitoring financial information.Advanced level of use and understanding of Microsoft Office (Excel and Word).Bachelor's degree in Engineering or similarStrong interpersonal and organization skills required, demonstrating competence in a rapidly changing, growth environment.Strong customer service focus is required.Strong interpersonal skills; able to effectively influence others through positive, proactive communication style;Excellent written and oral communication skills and sound problem-solving and decision making capabilities.Adept at dealing with all levels of management, possessing strong consultative and communication skills; Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Property & Facilities Management - Director </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>758</id>
        <date>2019-10-30 23:17:01</date>
        <title>
            Assistant Project Manager - Timberframe Residential experience
        </title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=758&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Jersey City, New Jersey</location>
        <description>
            We are seeking an Assistant Project Manager - Construction to join our client's team fast growing team! You will oversee project planning, scheduling, budgeting, and implementation. General Contractor based in Jersey City who is working on ground up mid-rise timber frame/stick built buildings Responsibilities * Oversee all aspects of construction project from planning to implementation for residential construction projects* Assist with Submittals and change orders * Allocate resources for assigned projects * Supervise onsite personnel and subcontractors * Interface with project inspectors, contractors, architects, engineers, city and county officials, and clients * Negotiate with contractors to receive reasonable order costs * Maintain high standards of workmanship that adhere to original plans and specifications Qualifications * Previous experience in construction management for a GC or developer * 2 to 5 years experience and experience with residential new build projects* College degree in Construction strongly preferred Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Assistant Project Manager</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>756</id>
        <date>2019-10-30 22:32:15</date>
        <title>Director of Facilities Management</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=756&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>New Jersey, New York</location>
        <description>
            Director of Facilities ManagementMiddletown, New Jersey Healthcare Resourcing Group is working in partnership with a not for profit organization, who provides services that includes Senior Living Facilities, Acute Care, Neuroscience and Maternity Health among other services. We are recruiting a Director of Facilities Management to hold responsibility for the management team and staff, coordinating all activities within the Building Services Department whilst operationalizing the department service objectives. We are seeking a Director to motivate, coach and reward the department, ensuring full compliance with federal, state and local regulations. Responsibilities;Hold responsibility for the Quality Control Program, monitoring departmental operations and recommend changes where necessary to optimize quality of services.Plan and control the department activities consistent manner, in-line with departmental goals.Assign work and supervise staff.Maintains flow and quality of work to assure timely completion of assigned workload and adherence to standards of quality control.Review and evaluate existing company methods, systems, practices and procedures.Acts as a technical resource to staff and resolves problems or refers to the department head as appropriate.Implement any new or modified methods, systems, practices and procedures.Hold regular staff meetings to keep employees up to date on any changes or relevant issues.Monitor employee work to ensure performance standards are maintained.Maintain working knowledge of all mechanical, electrical and auxiliary functions.Inspect any completed work to ensure finished product complies with quality standards.Oversee the follow up with departments to ensure work orders are completed in required timescales.Monitor and coordinate preventative maintenance and building repair and improvement projects, including any construction projects performed by vendors/contractors.Inspect completed work by vendors to ensure project is completed to specifications.Negotiate with vendors for preferred agreements.Write specifications for corrective maintenance and construction/renovation projects.Respond immediately to drills and emergencies, demonstrate knowledge of emergency procedures.Prepare and maintain department records in compliance with JCAHO and Department of Health Standards and local authorities. Qualifications &amp; Experience;Bachelor's Degree in Engineering required, Masters preferred.Minimum of 5 years maintenance management experience, preferably within a health care institution.Knowledge of construction project management.Ability to read, comprehend, and transmit detailed instructions in writing and verbally. Hold thorough knowledge of building trades (carpentry, painting, electrical, plumbing, HVAC, and mechanical) required.Strong organizational, and interpersonal skills to effectively relate with all members of the healthcare team.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Director of Facilities Management , Property & Facilities Management - Vice President Facilities Services, Property & Facilities Management - Director
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>755</id>
        <date>2019-10-30 22:21:30</date>
        <title>Project Manager - Construction</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=755&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Brooklyn, New York</location>
        <description>
            We are seeking a Project Manager - Construction to join our client's team fast growing team! General Contractor based in Brooklyn who has a New Commercial building being built.Responsibilities Work with superintendents and trades to plan, organize and direct activities concerned with construction projects. Establish project objectives, policies, procedures and performance standards within boundaries of company policy and contract specifications. Confer with owners, supervisors and foremen to discuss such matters as work procedures, complaints and construction problems. Initiate and maintain liaison with owners and other contacts to facilitate project activities. Monitor and control project through administrative direction of superintendent/assistant superintendent to ensure project is completed on schedule and within budget. Investigate potentially serious situations and brainstorms corrective measures. Represent company in project meetings, attend strategy meetings and maintain customer relations and when conducting meetings. Work with contract administrator to manage financial aspects of contracts to protect company's interest and simultaneously maintain good relationship with the customer. Interpret and explain plans and contract terms to administrative staff, workers and clients. Formulate reports concerning such areas as work progress, costs and scheduling.Coordinates with owner in ensuring that the property complies with the codes and regulations of each agency having jurisdiction over the property.Meets with external organizations to perform a detailed inspection of property ensure building codes are met. Work with subcontractors to assign workers to construction sites to work on specified projects.Makes timely decisions using sound and accurate judgment while keeping appropriate parties informed in the decision-making process.Identifies problems then gathers and analyzes information skillfully. Consults with entities associated with and affected by issue.Qualifications Previous experience in construction management for a GC or developer Familiarity with construction management software2 to 7 years experience and experience with commercial new build projectsCollege degree in Construction strongly preferredResourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Project Manager </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>754</id>
        <date>2019-10-30 21:00:31</date>
        <title>Chief Building Engineer</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=754&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>California, California</location>
        <description>
            Chief Building EngineerIntegrated Facilities Management FirmPasadena, CA The Chief Building Engineer is responsible for daily operations of property portfolio, including HVAC, mechanical, electrical, plumbing, lighting equipment and controls, Chilled Water Systems, Air Handlers, Boilers, Heat Exchangers, Air Handler Units (AHU), Variable Air Volume (VAV) Systems, Fan Coil Units (FCU), fire and safety systems, refrigeration equipment and various other mechanical, electrical systems, in such a manner as to ensure optimal conditions. Provides Operations &amp; Maintenance (O&amp;M) for building systems of other facilities as assigned or directed. Will work with Property Manager to develop and manage annual repairs and maintenance budgets. The Chief Building Engineer will also help mentor engineering staff and manage vendors to coordinate preventative maintenance, tenant improvements, and special projects.This position will require overseeing over 150,000 square feet of office &amp; laboratories located in the Thousand Oaks, Culver City and Pasadena areas. Duties;Experience in a Laboratory / Clean Room environment a plus.Aware of and comply with Government, State, City, Company, and client policies, procedures and regulations.Provide an exceptional level of customer service to the clients.Maintain and keep up to date with building systems technology.Ensure buildings are in strict accordance with fire and safety codes.Lab equipment technician or building automation/controls technician.Responds in a professional, polite, and helpful manner when dealing with clients.Will act as the primary liaison with the client.Ability to work independently and as part of a larger team.Strong collaboration skills.Proficient knowledge of Microsoft Word, Excel and Outlook is required.Able to effectively interact with clients, field staff, co-workers and vendors.Strong verbal, written, analytical, and interpersonal skills.Maintains a clean and professional appearance.Participates in training directed at increasing job-related skills.Works according to schedule prepared and distributed by Leadership.Works with and takes direction from Leadership.Ability to lift, push, pull, and/ or carry minimum 50lbs.Ability to bend, squat, reach, kneel on a daily basis.Will manage a team of cleaners on site.Completes work order by utilizing a computerized maintenance work order system.Ensure Mechanical/ Electrical/ Storage space are kept neat, clean, orderly, and safe.Ability bid out, select, and manage outside vendors.Familiar with operations and troubleshooting of HVAC controls.Troubleshooting ability with various equipment and voltages up to 600 VAC.Responds to after-hour unscheduled emergencies as needed.Know and understand the Owner's Building Operations/ Rules for the building(s) under your assignment as provided by Leadership.Report inventory of; spare parts, tools, and service equipment to Leadership.Ensure all spare parts, tools, and service equipment are kept in a neat and orderly manner.Dispose of unusable spare parts under Leadership direction.Performs other tasks as instructed including but not limited to plumbing, carpentry, general building maintenance, and assists other trades as necessary. Qualifications;High School diploma or equivalent, 2-year Technical accreditation preferredMinimum 7 years' experience in property and/or facilities maintenance preferredValid driver's license and clean driving record requiredUniversal EPA Refrigerant Handler &amp; HVAC License requiredResourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Chief Engineer, Property & Facilities Management - Building Engineer
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>753</id>
        <date>2019-10-30 20:55:33</date>
        <title>Senior Project Manager - Construction Residential</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=753&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Brooklyn, New York</location>
        <description>
            My client is looking for a Senior Project Manager to be a part of their New York City office. They are a large General Contracting firm with offices in New York and New Jersey, specializing in all aspects of Residential, Commercial, Industrial and Institutional Construction. Over the last 25 years they have grown to annual gross of more than $300M.This is an exciting opportunity for an experienced Senior Project Manager with a strong background in high rise residential projects based in the five boroughs.Project DetailsStart Date - Dec/Jan Project Value - $250M Location - Brooklyn Size - 800,000 SF 2 High Rise Residential Towers 30 story &amp; 40 storyDuties and Responsibilities: * Planning and strategy of project development from the design effort through construction, obtaining Certificate of Occupancy and project closeout. * Oversight and coordination of the design development with the design team from schematic design to 100% CDs with development of project scopes of work. * Coordination with expeditors for plan review/approvals with the NYC DOB and permitting of project. * Management and coordination with the selected construction manager/general contractor to keep the project within established schedule and budget constraints. * Cost reporting of the project; tracking consultant contracts and construction schedule of values. * Reporting to the Senior Project Execultive.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Project Manager </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>752</id>
        <date>2019-10-30 13:33:12</date>
        <title>Licensed HVAC Journeyman Technician</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=752&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>50</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Worcester, Massachusetts</location>
        <description>
            Licensed HVAC TechnicianMassachusetts$38-42ph Resourcing Group is working with a global leader within the integrated facilities management industry. Working with a leading client within their respected industry, we have an exciting opportunity for a Massachusetts licensed HVAC Technician to become a vital part of an established but still growing division within a global business. Responsibilities: Support the maintenance of refrigeration and HVAC for a group of retail locationsBe proactive in refrigerant leak checking and repairsPerform HVAC/R preventive maintenance checks in a timely manner as assignedMonitor and log refrigerant usage within assigned storesCommunicate as needed with retail store location personnel to maintain refrigerated product integrityEstablish excellent customer service through effective and regular communication with store leadership to ensure they are kept informed of all on-going maintenance activitiesLiaise with store leadership to ensure that all planned maintenance activities are communicated effectivelyProvide all required job updates on a timely basis through City's job management portalMaintain all assets for which you have responsibility to the highest standardsMaintain clean and safe conditions in machine and electrical roomsAssist with trouble shooting problemsParticipate in company's "on call" after hours emergency call programComplete equipment inventories as assignedTravel between a group of stores within your area of responsibility Required Qualifications: Journeyman licensed in refrigeration and HVAC systems for the state of MAE.P.A. certified for refrigerant handling Class I &amp; II, or UniversalPossess a valid driver's license with a good driving record The Package:A highly competitive hourly rate.Over time paid at 1.5x.New vehicle with brand new tools.iPhone and iPad.Market leading medical insurance.401k matched to 5%28 days PTOResourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Maintenance Technician/Handyman , Property & Facilities Management - Maintenance/Engineering Supervisor , Property & Facilities Management - Building Engineer
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>751</id>
        <date>2019-10-25 17:25:35</date>
        <title>Construction Estimator - Boston - $120k</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=751&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Boston, Massachusetts</location>
        <description>
            Construction Estimator - Boston - $120k I am currently working with a established Boston GC, who are looking to hire a up and coming Estimator who is interested in joining a company with fast-track career progression. Due to work load and multiple project wins they are looking add a Estimator to their team. This hire will not only be an integral part of the company, but they will need to have the ambition to help grow the Estimating team and in the future be the lead company Estimator for the Boston office. The work is predominately working within ground up construction, covering a number of sectors including, high end, beach side multi-family Cape Cod, and Boston Homes, Commercial Office, institutional &amp; Commercial, and Multi-Family. Projects will range in value from $5m to $50m. This is a fantastic opportunity for any Estimator looking to forward there career, and work for a people friendly company with excellent benefits. Salary Range from - $100k - $120k (Experience Depending) , 401, health care, bonus. Please could we set up a call to discuss the company in more detail, or to apply, please email your resume to ian.crosby@resourcinggroup.us or call 646 515 1796 to discuss the position.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Estimator</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>750</id>
        <date>2019-10-25 16:42:25</date>
        <title>Estimator - Manhattan - $100k</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=750&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            Estimator - Manhattan - $100kMy client is a Manhattan based International Construction Consulting firm that provides project management, cost management and estimating, to clients involved in major construction projects worldwide. My client has long standing relationships with major global blue chip clients, that they win regular repeat business with. They are looking for an Estimator with 2-3 years experience from either a consultancy or GC background. This consultancy has a large portfolio of blue chip and NASDAQ-100 clients and work across all major industries and large schemes. Major Duties include: Produce concept level estimates to aid feasibility studies and assist with business cases, leveraging a range of information from simple internal benchmarking to detailed market data and estimates taken from drawings and specifications. Issue recommendations for the application of a estimator to produce costing of greater detail; incorporate estimator into project team - manage performance of estimating tasks/deliverables.Evaluate project scope and client needs to develop and present recommended budgets for necessary pre-bid and pre-construction cost estimating and cost planning services. Partner with project team to source and oversee the pre-bid and pre-construction services associated with the development of a project budget and cost plan.If you would like to apply for this position, please email your resume to ian.crosby@resourcinggroup.us or call 646 515 1796 to discuss in more detail.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Estimator</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>749</id>
        <date>2019-10-25 16:40:26</date>
        <title>Senior Estimator - White Plains - NY - $150k</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=749&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>White Plains, New York</location>
        <description>
            Senior Estimator - White Plains - NY - $150kMy client are one of the fastest growing civil engineering contractors in New York, the role will be based in the Head office near White Plains. They are looking to recruit a reputable Senior Estimator to work along the Estimating Director. The ideal candidate will be knowledgeable with the means and methods with clearing, demo, earthworks, underground utilities, Paving, site concrete. They would have worked on projects to the value of $20million and ideally have local knowledge around the New York area, with experience on ground down site / excavation projects. My clients team up with numerous local architects, engineers, and multiple municipalities on various projects. In addition to there general contracting services, this construction leading firm has a complete site work division; they own and operate an extensive fleet of trucks, heavy machinery and drilling equipment, self-performing all site work. My client offer a competitive compensation package with benefits tailored to the skills, experience, and contribution of the candidate. They are looking to pay up $150k as a base salary If you would like to discuss this position in more detail or apply for the position, please email me on ian.crosby@resourcinggroup.us with an updated resume or call 646 515 1796 to discuss.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Estimator</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>748</id>
        <date>2019-10-25 16:26:16</date>
        <title>
            Estimator - New York - Construction Consultancy - $80k
        </title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=748&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            Estimator - New York - Construction Consultancy - $80kMy client is looking for Estimators to be a part of our New York City construction consulting team. They are looking to hire motivated recent graduates of engineering, architecture, and construction project management programs for an Estimator position. This role is a excellent opportunity for someone that is looking to work with a team of highly motivated individuals, on intriguing projects in locations across the US. There could potentially be some oversees travel, as my client has also has worked on prestige projects in Mexico, Europe, Dubai, and the Caribbean.My client is looking for Estimators to accurately evaluate damaged structures and to then return to our NYC headquarters to compile a scope of repair and cost projections. They specialize in evaluating damage to buildings and structures. We have assessed damages to sky scrapers, bridges, marinas, theme parks, stadiums, even an indoor ski slope. Sometimes damages are caused by flooding, a hurricane, a factory fire, or possibly a design failure.This is fantastic opportunity to fast track your career in a fast paced construction environment. My client has a great culture within there modern midtown head office and are growing rapidly.Package:$80k401KHealth CareFree Breakfast with coffeeUp to 40% bonusCareer progressionPlease email your resume to ian.crosby@resourcinggroup.us or call 646 515 1796 to discuss.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Estimator</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>747</id>
        <date>2019-10-25 16:22:25</date>
        <title>Estimator - Long Island - New York - $140k</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=747&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>New York, New York</location>
        <description>
            Estimator - Long Island - New York - $140kI am currently working with a long standing, General Contracting and Design/Build firm, serving the New York metropolitan area, who are based in Long Island. Due to work load and multiple project wins they are looking add a Estimator to there fast growing Estimating Department. The work is predominately working within new construction and building renovations, shopping centres and malls, individual retail stores, educational and institutional facilities, industrial facilities, office building construction and fit-outs, hotels and apartment buildings. Projects will range in value from $5m to $65m.This is a excellent opportunity to fast track your career. But you will be joining an established business, with a very healthy order book already in place. My client has long standing relationships with major clients, that they win regular repeat business with. The also do a lot of major work across the leisure industry. Working on private golf clubs, country clubs, hotels, ground up and renovation projects. Projects will range in value from $5m to $50m.This is a fantastic opportunity for any Estimator to forward there career, and work for a people friendly company with excellent benefits.Salary Range from - $130k - $150k (Experience Depending)If you would like to apply for this position, please email your resume to ian.crosby@resourcinggroup.us or call 646 515 1796 to discuss in more detail.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Estimator</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>746</id>
        <date>2019-10-25 16:19:39</date>
        <title>Estimator - Manhattan - $140k</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=746&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            Estimator - Manhattan - $140kI am currently working with a long standing, leading New York ground up contractor who have been established 35 years. Due to work load and multiple project wins they are looking for a Estimator, as they expand there team. The work is predominately working within the residential affordable housing sector.This is a excellent opportunity to fast track your career. But you will be joining an established business, with a very healthy order book already in place. A leader in the mixed-income, affordable, supportive and institutional housing sectors and as a partner of the New York City and State housing agencies. This is a fantastic opportunity for any Estimator to forward there career, and work for a people friendly company with excellent benefits.Salary Range from - $140k (Experience Depending)If you would like to apply for this position, please email your resume to ian.crosby@resourcinggroup.us or call 646 515 1796 to discuss in more detail.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Estimator</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>745</id>
        <date>2019-10-25 16:16:38</date>
        <title>Senior Estimator - Manhattan - $170k</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=745&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            Senior Estimator - Manhattan - $170kI am currently working with a long standing, leading New York ground up contractor who have been established 60 years. Due to work load and multiple project wins they are looking for a Senior Estimator, as they expand there team. The work is covering a wide range of sectors, including, health care, education, residential, fit-out, industrial, and retail.This is a excellent opportunity to fast track your career. You will be joining an established business, with a very healthy order book already in place. My client work as the construction managers as well as the GC's and have a excellent reputation across New York.This is a fantastic opportunity for any Estimator to forward there career, and work for a people friendly company with excellent benefits.Salary Range from - $160k - $170k (Experience Depending)If you would like to apply for this position, please email your resume to ian.crosby@resourcinggroup.us or call 646 515 1796 to discuss in more detail.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Estimator</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>744</id>
        <date>2019-10-21 21:45:27</date>
        <title>Licensed HVAC Technician</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=744&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>50</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Massachusetts, Massachusetts</location>
        <description>
            Licensed HVAC Technician Massachusetts$38-42ph Resourcing Group is working with a global leader within the integrated facilities management industry. Working with a leading client within their respected industry, we have an exciting opportunity for a Massachusetts licensed HVAC Technician to become a vital part of an established but still growing division within a global business. Job Summary:The licensed HVAC mechanic is responsible for general maintenance, repairs and installations of HVAC systems. Operates, tests and overhauls a variety of air conditioning, ventilation, refrigeration systems and associated equipment. Assists the HVAC supervisor in the training of new personnel on equipment and systems. Performs tasks within capabilities involving piping systems, motors and controllers, pneumatic systems, chilled water, etc. Essential Responsibilities: Performs all repairs and maintenance of all heating/cooling and ventilating components common to the building operations.Operates, installs, repairs and maintains mechanical equipment such as air handlers, exhaust fans, automatic valves, pneumatic and electrical controls, refrigeration systems, space heating and cooling units..Required to respond to emergencies such as floods, power outages, etc. during off shift hours, if directed to by the department supervisorSnow removal is also the responsibility of the Maintenance Department and all Maintenance employees are required to participate.Performs record keeping requirements and written reports as part of a daily routine. Required Qualifications: Vocational or Technical training in HVAC required.License Mass. Refrigeration Tech Licen required, and Certificate 1 CFC Universal Certificate required.3-5 years related work experience required.Excellent familiarity with Building Automation Systems.Experienced in brazing, silver solder and performing pipe alterations.Experience with computer systems required, including web based applications and some Microsoft Office applications which may include Outlook, Word, Excel, PowerPoint or Access. Competencies: Decision Making:Ability to make decisions that are guided by general instructions and practices requiring some interpretation. May make recommendations for solving problems of moderate complexity and importance. Problem Solving:Ability to address problems that are varied, requiring analysis or interpretation of the situation using direct observation, knowledge and skills based on general precedents.Independence of Action: Ability to follow precedents and procedures. May set priorities and organize work within general guidelines. Seeks assistance when confronted with difficult and/or unpredictable situations. Work progress is monitored by supervisor/manager. Written Communications:Ability to communicate clearly and effectively in written English with internal and external customers. Oral Communications:Ability to comprehend and converse in English to communicate effectively with medical center staff, patients, families and external customers. The Package:A highly competitive hourly rate.Over time paid at 1.5x.New vehicle with brand new tools.iPhone and iPad.Market leading medical insurance.401k matched to 5%28 days PTO Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Maintenance Technician/Handyman , Property & Facilities Management - Building Engineer
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>742</id>
        <date>2019-10-16 14:31:37</date>
        <title>Mailroom Assistant</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=742&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>50,001 – 75,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Temporary</jobtype>
        <location>Denver, Colorado</location>
        <description>
            Job Title: Mailroom AssistantLocation: Denver, ColoradoSalary: $35,000 to $45,000Job Type: Temporary, 6 months on-going contractBenefits: Overtime, sick pay and medicalStart Date: October 2019 Resourcing Group is working in partnership with a global facilities management service provider who is looking to hire for the position Mailroom Assistant Main Responsibilities: Manages all components of the mailroom for both internal and external audiences, to include shipping, assembly, deliveries, mailing and packaging.Maintain postage meter, handle postage monies, install updates, and arrange service callsManage vendor accounts and generate reports, as necessaryLead and supervise elements in the Mail Room area to include scheduling and supervising worksEnsure work areas and storage facilities are properly maintained, organized and cleanProcess mail and packages for shipmentProactively work to manage and develop the relationship with the client, customer and vendorsAssist with any administrative and clerical requirements including the co-ordination of deliveries, mail and courier servicesAssist with projects and functions that the department is tasked to organize, including meeting room assistanceManage the maintenance of all mail equipment and arrange service calls where necessaryFully and proactively contribute to ISO 14001 accreditation which may include periodic site inspections and audits combined with meeting HSE legislationEnhance processes to support and facilitate customer service deliveryComply with all Health &amp; Safety legislationProvide guidance, instruction, and supervise Mailroom AssistantSupport Reproduction Center at times of high volume.Order and manage inventory of supplies, special projects, shipping and mailing, as requested by management Essential Requirements: High School Graduate2 years minimum related mail room / building maintenance experience1 years Facilities management / Assistance experience To apply for this post, please respond to this advert by sending us your most up to date resume or contact Jayde Edgley on 646 595 7464 Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Business in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Facilities Co-ordinator
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>741</id>
        <date>2019-10-11 19:47:13</date>
        <title>Continuous Improvement Manager - Facilities</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=741&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Texas, Texas</location>
        <description>
            Job Title: Continuous Improvement Manager - FacilitiesLocation: Houston, TexasSalary: $75,000 to $95,000Job Type: Permanent, Full timeBenefits: Vacation, Sick Leave, 401k, MedicalStart Date: November 2019 Resourcing Group is working in partnership with a global facilities management service provider who is looking to hire for the position Continuous Improvement Manager within the Oil &amp; Gas Industry Main Responsibilities: Overall project delivery of the continuous improvement program to drive productivity and quality improvements using Lean or Six Sigma practices Drive the continuous improvement of processes, working practices, systems and Property delivery strategy within a company, and implement programs that will have continuing long-term benefitsDevelop plans, schedules, and budgets for projects to improve existing processes and our approach to deliver the services to our key stakeholdersSupervise and direct the work of CI initiatives with facilities staff, promote best practices and work with the team to effect positive changes in the workplaceContinuously review and monitor existing processes to make sure they continue to perform at optimal levels of efficiencyManage periodic updates to the stakeholdersMaintain the resource plan and clear accountability of the project team members.Support the Regional Facilities Site Managers to set the change agendaWork with other departmental managers to address the mindsets and behavior changes required in their respective departments to sustain the changeAlignment of the World Class Service approach across the regionPromote the implementation of Lean, Six-Sigma (or other equivalent CI) best practicesContribute to the development, identification and dissemination of best practicesIdentify, promote and arrange benchmarking visits with other sitesContribute to the development of the CI program within the region and support local teams to drive excellenceAssist with management of supply chain partners supporting services - PPM &amp; reactive within the client space as neededCommunication - 3600 cascading information to customers, peers and team whilst keeping management team fully informed Essential Requirements: A Bachelor's degree5 years minimum experience in a similar role supporting continuous improvement within a facilities management environmentLean or Six Sigma certificationFM or project management experienceSoftware and systems experience using MS Office and MS ProjectChange management experience is a plus To apply for this post, please respond to this advert by sending us your most up to date resume or contact Jayde Edgley on 646 846 6634 or 646 595 7464. Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Facilities Manager
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>740</id>
        <date>2019-10-10 21:45:05</date>
        <title>Facilities and Mailroom Supervisor</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=740&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>35,001 – 50,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Temporary</jobtype>
        <location>Denver, Colorado</location>
        <description>
            Job Title: Facilities and Mailroom SupervisorLocation: Denver, ColoradoSalary: $35,000 to $40,000Job Type: Temporary, 3-6 months on-going contractBenefits: Overtime, sick pay and medicalStart Date: October 2019 Resourcing Group is working in partnership with a global facilities management service provider who is looking to hire for the position Facilities and Mailroom Supervisor Main Responsibilities: Manages all components of the mailroom for both internal and external audiences, to include shipping, assembly, deliveries, mailing and packaging.Maintain postage meter, handle postage monies, install updates, and arrange service callsManage vendor accounts and generate reports, as necessaryLead and supervise elements in the Mail Room area to include scheduling and supervising worksEnsure work areas and storage facilities are properly maintained, organized and cleanProcess mail and packages for shipmentProactively work to manage and develop the relationship with the client, customer and vendorsAssist with any administrative and clerical requirements including the co-ordination of deliveries, mail and courier servicesAssist with projects and functions that the department is tasked to organize, including meeting room assistanceManage the maintenance of all mail equipment and arrange service calls where necessaryFully and proactively contribute to ISO 14001 accreditation which may include periodic site inspections and audits combined with meeting HSE legislationEnhance processes to support and facilitate customer service deliveryComply with all Health &amp; Safety legislationProvide guidance, instruction, and supervise Mailroom AssistantSupport Reproduction Center at times of high volume.Order and manage inventory of supplies, special projects, shipping and mailing, as requested by management Essential Requirements: High School Graduate3 years minimum related mail room / building maintenance experience2 years Facilities management / Assistance experience To apply for this post, please respond to this advert by sending us your most up to date resume or contact Jayde Edgley on 646 595 7464 Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Business in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Facilities Co-ordinator
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>739</id>
        <date>2019-10-10 20:43:01</date>
        <title>Project Manager - Facilities</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=739&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Temporary</jobtype>
        <location>Texas, Texas</location>
        <description>
            Job Title: Project ManagerLocation: Houston, TexasSalary: $100,000 to $125,000Job Type: Temporary, 6-12 months on-going contractBenefits: Overtime, sick pay and medicalStart Date: October / November 2019 Resourcing Group is working in partnership with a global facilities management service provider who is looking to hire for the position Project Manager who will manage various projects for clients including design, facilities, construction, occupancy, and budget management. Main Responsibilities: Interfaces with clients to define project requirements. Establishes project work plan and deadlines. Creates persuasive presentations that meet the project's objectives.Tracks progress of projects against goals, objectives, timelines, and budgets, and generate reports on status.Monitors expenses to ensure they fall within the prescribed budget.Manages all facets of project design, construction, and occupancy.Manages project team by providing direction and leadership.Facilitates client meetings regarding project matters. Manages all phases of project management including design, construction, occupancy, quality control, staffing, and budget management.Manage multiple interior fit out projects valued between $1M to $3M and 1M sqftWorks closely with other functional areas of the organization, project contractors, internal team members, external collaborators, customers and suppliers. Essential Requirements: A Bachelor's degree10 years minimum related project experiencethe ability to read, analyze, and interpret general business periodicals, professional journals, technical procedures, or governmental regulations;Write procedure manuals; and to effectively present information and respond to questions from groups of managers, clients, customers, and the general public.Requires in-depth knowledge of financial terms and principles and the ability to forecast and prepare budgets. Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Business in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Property & Facilities Management</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>737</id>
        <date>2019-10-09 19:41:48</date>
        <title>Senior Facilities Manager</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=737&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            Senior Facilities Manager - CommercialNew York City$120k - $150k Working with a well known integrated facilities management firm who are experiencing fantastic growth across the US, this is a crucial role within the business.Our client has a history of managing high class real estate and are looking to add a senior facilities professional to their team, working with one of their key clients. The Senior Facilities Manager will be based at the client's offices and will oversee the delivery of facilities operations across a small portfolio of location around the City. The portfolio is predominantly high end, versatile commercial office space, in excess of 1M sf.Key duties for the Senior Facilities Manager will include, developing the partnership and relationship with the client, managing the in-house facilities team, establishing scope of works, all whilst ensuring slick building operations.Experience required;6+ years facilities experience at a senior level.Proven experience managing a large facilities contract ideally with a third party service provide.Accreditation from IFMA, BOMA or other industry associations is beneficial, but not essential.Degree BA educated is preferred.To be considered for this position, please submit your resume.If you would like more information on this, or any other vacancies, please contact Matt Allen on 646 891 4639.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Vice President Facilities Services, Property & Facilities Management - Senior Facilities Manager, Property & Facilities Management - Regional Facilities Manger
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>736</id>
        <date>2019-10-08 22:55:41</date>
        <title>Superintendent - Wood Frame</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=736&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>New Jersey, New York</location>
        <description>
            My client a national leader in multifamily real estate, offering expertise in property management, investment management, and development and construction of rental housing. Currently are recruiting for a project Superintendent to work on projects based in the Central New Jersey area. All projects are mid to low rise timber frame/stick built so experience in these builds is essential.In this role you will:Build and maintain project scheduleResponsible to notify subcontractors early when their services are required onsite.Responsible for notifying the office if obstacles to on-time completion occur.Review all submittals with Project Engineer.Review plans for deficiencies and changes.Generate RFI's.Review owner contract with Project ManagerReview and prepare subcontractors with Project ManagerApprove subcontractor payments with Project Manager.Review and approve PCO's and pay applications with Project ManagerResponsible for owner satisfaction of the assigned projects.Responsible review budget on a monthly basis as well as all invoices approved, and the owner billing reviewed and approved.Monitor trade compliance with project safety program requirements; document and ensure corrective measures are implemented and overall quality of their work being performed.Generate agenda and conduct weekly safety and progress meetings with subcontractor's and foremen.Set up jobsite trailer, power and phones.Generate daily reports, look ahead schedule and weekly status updates.Schedule and monitor city and special inspectionsPrepare as-builts and provide any city required reports to obtain a Certificate of Occupancy.Provide as-builts and any required reports to Project Coordinator, along with job files, for project close out. Plan and supervise Assistant Construction Manager and/or trade activities including: determining method of construction, manpower levels, material quantities equipment, temporary power sources, work schedule and documenting actual hours worked.Perform additional assignments per supervisor's direction.The Successful ApplicantWill have 5+ years experience as a project superintendentMust have proven track record of working on timber frame/stick built projectsSolid knowledge and understanding of the development and new construction business from both a technical standpoint, and from a project management standpoint.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Superintendent </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>735</id>
        <date>2019-10-08 00:50:51</date>
        <title>Facilities Manager</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=735&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Texas, Texas</location>
        <description>
            Job Title: Facilities ManagerSalary: $75,000 to $95,000 + full benefits and bonus Location: Houston, TexasJob Type: Permanent, Monday to Friday 8:00am to 17:00pmStart Date: 28th October / ASAP Resourcing Group is working in partnership with a global investment management firm in Houston, Texas.They are looking to hire an experienced Facilities Manager who will provide highly professional and efficient facilities management services to this corporate client.Main Responsibilities:Effectively managing vendors and the facilities management team, ensuring quality of services are provided to a 500,000 square foot officeMinimize risk and maintain or improve profitability against agreed targetsBudget and financial reporting to the Senior FMRelationship management - client, ,supplier and team relationsManaging the existing facilities team of 12 staff, responsible for performance management, training and hiringContinually improve and exceed customer expectationsNetworking within the industry and identifying new opportunities within the market Essential Requirements:Bachelors Degree5 years minimum facilities management experience2 year experience managing a facilities teamEstablished network within the facilities management industryIFMA membership and/or FM certification desirable To apply for this post, please respond to this advert by sending us your most up to date resume or contact Jayde Edgley on 646 595 7464 or 646 846 6634 Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Facilities Manager
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>734</id>
        <date>2019-10-03 23:05:10</date>
        <title>MEP Superintendent</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=734&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            Lead MEP Superintendent is responsible for the overall mechanical, electrical, and plumbing field work on a project, ensuring that company policies and procedures are met in regard to safety, scheduling, budget, quality and customer satisfaction.Responsibilities Direct the day-to-day coordination of MEP trade contractors and their sub-contractors to ensure they turn out high-quality work that meets the approved project scheduleDevelop, document and communicate the work plan regarding changes made in the fieldMaintain a thorough understanding of contract documents to be able to plan ahead and anticipate potential problems before they ariseObtain or verify that the subcontractors obtain all necessary permits for construction purposesAct as primary safety representative in the field and enforce quality control policiesEstablish credibility among Owners, trade contractors, unions etc. by maintaining a fair and trustworthy environmentLead contractor meetings on a regular basisCreate, manage and update the project schedule, create and implement contingency plans when necessaryCommunicate schedule status, updates and changes to Project Team and Trade ContractorsResolve jurisdictional disputesEXPERIENCE/EDUCATIONComprehensive knowledge of MEP systems in Construction Management delivery methods5-10 years experience on $15 million or larger commercial/industrial construction projects in a superintendent role KNOWLEDGE, SKILLS &amp; ABILITIESKnowledge of Prolog, Primavera Scheduling, CMIC preferredConstruction-document and drawing literate, with knowledge of all phases of constructionExperience and proficiency in all divisions of work, methods, materials, scheduling, and cost controlOSHA 30 hour certifiedResourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>733</id>
        <date>2019-10-03 21:48:50</date>
        <title>Project Manager - Construction</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=733&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Brooklyn, New York</location>
        <description>
            We are seeking a Project Manager - Construction to join our client's team fast growing team! You will oversee project planning, scheduling, budgeting, and implementation. General Contractor based in Brooklyn who has a New Commercial building being built.Responsibilities * Oversee all aspects of construction project from planning to implementation for commercial construction projects that are larger (10+) million. * Assist with Submittals and change orders * Allocate resources for assigned projects * Supervise onsite personnel and subcontractors * Interface with project inspectors, contractors, architects, engineers, city and county officials, and clients * Negotiate with contractors to receive reasonable order costs * Maintain high standards of workmanship that adhere to original plans and specifications Qualifications * Previous experience in construction management for a GC or developer * Familiarity with construction management software * 2 to 10 years experience and experience with commercial new build projects* College degree in Construction strongly preferred Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Project Manager </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>732</id>
        <date>2019-10-02 19:30:31</date>
        <title>Assistant Project Manager - Construction</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=732&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>New York, New York</location>
        <description>
            We are seeking an Assistant Project Manager - Construction to join our client's team fast growing team! You will oversee project planning, scheduling, budgeting, and implementation. General Contractor based in Long Island who is working on ground up warehouse and industrial projects.Responsibilities * Oversee all aspects of construction project from planning to implementation for commercial construction projects that are larger (10+) million. * Assist with Submittals and change orders * Allocate resources for assigned projects * Supervise onsite personnel and subcontractors * Interface with project inspectors, contractors, architects, engineers, city and county officials, and clients * Negotiate with contractors to receive reasonable order costs * Maintain high standards of workmanship that adhere to original plans and specifications Qualifications * Previous experience in construction management for a GC or developer * Familiarity with construction management software * 2 to 5 years experience and experience with commercial new build projects* College degree in Construction strongly preferred Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Assistant Project Manager</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>731</id>
        <date>2019-09-27 22:01:04</date>
        <title>Senior Estimator - Manhattan - $160k</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=731&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            Senior Estimator - Manhattan - $160kI am currently working with a long standing, leading New York ground up contractor who have been established 60 years. Due to work load and multiple project wins they are looking for a Senior Estimator, as they expand there team. The work is covering a wide range of sectors, including, health care, education, residential, fit-out, industrial, and retail.This is a excellent opportunity to fast track your career. You will be joining an established business, with a very healthy order book already in place. My client work as the construction managers as well as the GC's and have a excellent reputation across New York.This is a fantastic opportunity for any Estimator to forward there career, and work for a people friendly company with excellent benefits.Salary Range from - $160k (Experience Depending)If you would like to apply for this position, please email your resume to ian.crosby@resourcinggroup.us or call 646 515 1796 to discuss in more detail.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Estimator</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>730</id>
        <date>2019-09-27 21:34:03</date>
        <title>Estimator - Manhattan - $140k</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=730&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            Estimator - Manhattan - $140kI am currently working with a long standing, leading New York ground up contractor who have been established 35 years. Due to work load and multiple project wins they are looking for a Estimator, as they expand there team. The work is predominately working within the residential affordable housing sector.This is a excellent opportunity to fast track your career. But you will be joining an established business, with a very healthy order book already in place. A leader in the mixed-income, affordable, supportive and institutional housing sectors and as a partner of the New York City and State housing agencies. This is a fantastic opportunity for any Estimator to forward there career, and work for a people friendly company with excellent benefits.Salary Range from - $140k (Experience Depending)If you would like to apply for this position, please email your resume to ian.crosby@resourcinggroup.us or call 646 515 1796 to discuss in more detail.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Estimator</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>729</id>
        <date>2019-09-27 21:03:03</date>
        <title>Estimator - Long Island - New York - $140k</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=729&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>New York, New York</location>
        <description>
            Estimator - Long Island - New York - $140kI am currently working with a long standing, General Contracting and Design/Build firm, serving the New York metropolitan area, who are based in Long Island. Due to work load and multiple project wins they are looking add a Estimator to there fast growing Estimating Department. The work is predominately working within new construction and building renovations, shopping centres and malls, individual retail stores, educational and institutional facilities, industrial facilities, office building construction and fit-outs, hotels and apartment buildings. Projects will range in value from $5m to $65m.This is a excellent opportunity to fast track your career. But you will be joining an established business, with a very healthy order book already in place. My client has long standing relationships with major clients, that they win regular repeat business with. The also do a lot of major work across the leisure industry. Working on private golf clubs, country clubs, hotels, ground up and renovation projects. Projects will range in value from $5m to $50m.This is a fantastic opportunity for any Estimator to forward there career, and work for a people friendly company with excellent benefits.Salary Range from - $130k - $150k (Experience Depending)If you would like to apply for this position, please email your resume to ian.crosby@resourcinggroup.us or call 646 515 1796 to discuss in more detail.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Estimator</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>728</id>
        <date>2019-09-25 22:57:51</date>
        <title>Assistant Project Manager - Construction</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=728&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Brooklyn, New York</location>
        <description>
            We are seeking an Assistant Project Manager - Construction to join our client's team fast growing team! You will oversee project planning, scheduling, budgeting, and implementation. General Contractor based in Brooklyn who is working on affordable housing projects.Responsibilities * Oversee all aspects of construction project from planning to implementation for commercial construction projects that are larger (10+) million. * Assist with Submittals and change orders * Allocate resources for assigned projects * Supervise onsite personnel and subcontractors * Interface with project inspectors, contractors, architects, engineers, city and county officials, and clients * Negotiate with contractors to receive reasonable order costs * Maintain high standards of workmanship that adhere to original plans and specifications Qualifications * Previous experience in construction management for a GC or developer * Familiarity with construction management software * 2 to 10 years experience and experience with commercial new build projects* College degree in Construction strongly preferred Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Assistant Project Manager</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>727</id>
        <date>2019-09-25 22:40:00</date>
        <title>MEP Project Manager</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=727&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            Lead MEP Project Manager working for a large GC based in Manhattan. Your role will be responsible for the overall mechanical, electrical, and plumbing field work on a project, ensuring that company policies and procedures are met in regard to safety, scheduling, budget, quality and customer satisfaction.Responsibilities Direct the day-to-day coordination of MEP trade contractors and their sub-contractors to ensure they turn out high-quality work that meets the approved project scheduleDevelop, document and communicate the work plan regarding changes made in the fieldMaintain a thorough understanding of contract documents to be able to plan ahead and anticipate potential problems before they ariseObtain or verify that the subcontractors obtain all necessary permits for construction purposesAct as primary safety representative in the field and enforce quality control policiesEstablish credibility among Owners, trade contractors, unions etc. by maintaining a fair and trustworthy environmentLead contractor meetings on a regular basisCreate, manage and update the project schedule, create and implement contingency plans when necessaryCommunicate schedule status, updates and changes to Project Team and Trade ContractorsResolve jurisdictional disputesEXPERIENCE/EDUCATIONComprehensive knowledge of MEP systems in Construction Management delivery methods5-10 years experience on High Rise Residential Projects in Manhattan KNOWLEDGE, SKILLS &amp; ABILITIESKnowledge of Prolog, Primavera Scheduling, CMIC preferredConstruction-document and drawing literate, with knowledge of all phases of constructionExperience and proficiency in all divisions of work, methods, materials, scheduling, and cost controlOSHA 30 hour certifiedResourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - MEP Superintendent</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>726</id>
        <date>2019-09-25 21:31:21</date>
        <title>Senior Facilities Manager</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=726&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            Senior Facilities Manager - CommercialNew York City Working with a well known integrated facilities management firm who are experiencing fantastic growth across the US, this is a crucial role within the business. Our client has a history of managing high class real estate and are looking to add a senior facilities professional to their team, working with one of their key clients. The Senior Facilities Manager will be based at the client's offices and will oversee the delivery of facilities operations across a small portfolio of location around the City. The portfolio is predominantly high end, versatile commercial office space, in excess of 1M sf. Key duties for the Senior Facilities Manager will include, developing the partnership and relationship with the client, managing the in-house facilities team, establishing scope of works, all whilst ensuring slick building operations.Experience required;6+ years facilities experience at a senior level.Proven experience managing a large facilities contract ideally with a third party service provide.Accreditation from IFMA, BOMA or other industry associations is beneficial, but not essential.Degree BA educated is preferred. To be considered for this position, please submit your resume. If you would like more information on this, or any other vacancies, please contact Matt Allen on 646 891 4639.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management, Property & Facilities Management - Director of Facilities Management , Property & Facilities Management - Senior Facilities Manager
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>725</id>
        <date>2019-09-19 22:02:42</date>
        <title>Senior Facilities Director</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=725&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>New Jersey, New York</location>
        <description>
            Senior Facilities Director Our client is a self managed real estate investment trust and a leading provider of self storage facilities. With well over 1000 units across the nation (and still growing), this is an exciting opportunity to join a thriving business. The Senior Facilities Director directs approved processes and methods to ensure the completion of each direct report's job responsibilities for capital expenditure management of facility services operations. You will evaluate maintenance schedules for each property, the annual capital expenditure budgets and due diligence for potential acquisition sites. You will also supervise 5 Facility Managers and over 750 properties which vary on size and location. Key duties will include;Ensure capital expenditure projects are delivered on time and within budget.Continuous site improvement strategies for all properties, working across various sites and markets.Conduct regular reviews on each facility and management, providing training and development where necessary.Schedule capital improvement projects annually.Budget / actual expenditure; Monthly and year to date budget reviews, cost to manage expenses.Identify opportunities for improvement of systems, processes and training to improve personally and efficiencies.Work with JV, Acquisitions, Development teams to keep abreast of new projects and completion timescales.Manage and coordinate due diligence process for new and acquisition properties, including the preparation of capital expenditure projections.Visiting all existing and new sites to monitor quality of annual construction projects providing strategic direction and training to Facility Managers.Participate in monthly one to one meetings with Facility Services VP and Facility Managers.Work with departments including Marketing, HR, L&amp;D to ensure enhanced property performance.Act as key contact for third party owners and asset managers for JV partners.Travel throughout the east coast region to conduct training sessions and present at departmental meetings. Qualifications Needed;Bachelor's degree required.10 Years experience in multi location facility/construction management.Proven track record of managing multi facility service managers and real estate due diligence. In return, we can offer a great company culture and rewarding career path along with a competitive salary and benefits package. Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Director of Facilities Management , Property & Facilities Management - Vice President Facilities Services, Property & Facilities Management - Director , Property & Facilities Management - Director of Operations
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>724</id>
        <date>2019-09-19 16:45:13</date>
        <title>
            Estimator - New York - Construction Consultancy - $90k
        </title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=724&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            Estimator - New York - Construction Consultancy - $90kMy client is looking for Estimators to be a part of our New York City construction consulting team. They are looking to hire motivated recent graduates of engineering, architecture, and construction project management programs for an Estimator position. This role is a excellent opportunity for someone that is looking to work with a team of highly motivated individuals, on intriguing projects in locations across the US. There could potentially be some oversees travel, as my client has also has worked on prestige projects in Mexico, Europe, Dubai, and the Caribbean.My client is looking for Estimators to accurately evaluate damaged structures and to then return to our NYC headquarters to compile a scope of repair and cost projections. They specialize in evaluating damage to buildings and structures. We have assessed damages to sky scrapers, bridges, marinas, theme parks, stadiums, even an indoor ski slope. Sometimes damages are caused by flooding, a hurricane, a factory fire, or possibly a design failure.This is fantastic opportunity to fast track your career in a fast paced construction environment. My client has a great culture within there modern midtown head office and are growing rapidly.Package:$80K - $100k401KHealth CareFree Breakfast with coffeeUp to 40% bonusCareer progressionPlease email your resume to ian.crosby@resourcinggroup.us or call 646 515 1796 to discuss.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Estimator</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>723</id>
        <date>2019-09-19 16:42:53</date>
        <title>Senior Estimator - White Plains - NY - $150k</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=723&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>White Plains, New York</location>
        <description>
            Senior Estimator - White Plains - NY - $150kMy client are one of the fastest growing civil engineering contractors in New York, the role will be based in the Head office near White Plains. They are looking to recruit a reputable Senior Estimator to work along the Estimating Director. The ideal candidate will be knowledgeable with the means and methods with clearing, demo, earthworks, underground utilities, Paving, site concrete. They would have worked on projects to the value of $20million and ideally have local knowledge around the New York area, with experience on ground down site / excavation projects. My clients team up with numerous local architects, engineers, and multiple municipalities on various projects. In addition to there general contracting services, this construction leading firm has a complete site work division; they own and operate an extensive fleet of trucks, heavy machinery and drilling equipment, self-performing all site work. My client offer a competitive compensation package with benefits tailored to the skills, experience, and contribution of the candidate. They are looking to pay up $150k as a base salary If you would like to discuss this position in more detail or apply for the position, please email me on ian.crosby@resourcinggroup.us with an updated resume or call 646 515 1796 to discuss.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Estimator</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>722</id>
        <date>2019-09-12 16:28:28</date>
        <title>
            Construction Superintendent - Industrial Experience
        </title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=722&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Pennsylvania, Pennsylvania</location>
        <description>
            Resourcing Group are recruiting for several Superintendents to work for a medium sized general contractor based in Pennsylvania on warehouse build outs.The projects in particular are small to medium sized warehouse projects (50,000 to 300,000 SF buildings) where the Superintendent would be the company's lone representative onsite. Minimum Requirements;Superintendent capable of running their own project 5-10 years experience as a Superintendent Warehouse/Industrial/Big Box Retail experience would be ideal.Superintendents Responsibilities;Meeting or exceeding project schedule Ensuring that adequate subcontractor manpower is on site to support the project Communicating with Subcontractors, Project Manager, Design Professionals and Owner to proactively identify schedule obstacles and resolve those obstacles before they affect the projectAccurately documenting all T&amp;M ticket work on a daily basis and effectively communicate with PM to promptly issue change orders or resolve contract disputesDrafting site management plan (laydown, housekeeping, etc.) and enforce plan Participating in safety audits per Operations Group goalsEnsuring shutdown plans, lift plans, etc. are utilized per company guidelinesInspecting work installation for adherence to plans and specificationsUnderstanding status of submittalsUsing Prolog RFI's (Request for information) as necessary to clarify issuesDevelop a positive relationship with customers that are consistent with project objectives and directives.Participate in monthly invoice approval process for subcontractorsFulfill daily project related tasks thoroughly and efficientlyIdentify and resolve all potential problems and/or discrepancies contained in the contract documentsResponsible for field coordination not only between trades but including owner or owner resources.Responsible for insuring the accuracy of surveys and layout.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Superintendent </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>721</id>
        <date>2019-09-09 16:13:04</date>
        <title>Assistant Superintendent - Interiors</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=721&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            The Assistant Project Superintendent holds the responsibility and authority for the daily execution of a specific area or portion of the project to be carried out safely, within budget, on schedule, to the company's standard of quality and to the client's satisfaction.My client is a rapidly growing, highly diversified construction company who specialize in interior renovations.Responsibilities Responsible for general contract, subcontract documents, drawings and specifications under direction from the Superintendent.Check and verify subcontractor layout to ensure compliance with established control, line and grade.Monitor production and record rates in logbook to be used for future scheduling.Maintain a set of production documents and update daily so an accurate picture of work in place is consistently maintained.Report any and all field conditions and issues to the Superintendent.Monitor job progress on-site, checking all work to ensure compliance with contract documents and the Quality Control Program.Work with Superintendent to develop and carry out the plan and schedule for project work.Plan and prepare documentation to facilitate the close out process at the discretion of the Superintendent.Maintain and review the safety requirements for the Project and resolve or report deficiencies to the Superintendent and Safety Manager.Work with and coach field engineers on the project to facilitate their skills development.Assist in maintaining the Construction Management Plan and logistical co-ordination.Qualifications Bachelor's degree in Engineering or Construction Management preferred.3 to 5 years of experience in related construction fields.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Superintendent </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>720</id>
        <date>2019-09-06 21:04:22</date>
        <title>Estimator - Manhattan - $100k</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=720&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            Estimator - Manhattan - $100kMy client is a Manhattan based International Construction Consulting firm that provides project management, cost management and estimating, to clients involved in major construction projects worldwide. My client has long standing relationships with major global blue chip clients, that they win regular repeat business with. They are looking for an Estimator with 2-3 years experience from either a consultancy or GC background. This consultancy has a large portfolio of blue chip and NASDAQ-100 clients and work across all major industries and large schemes. Major Duties include: Produce concept level estimates to aid feasibility studies and assist with business cases, leveraging a range of information from simple internal benchmarking to detailed market data and estimates taken from drawings and specifications. Issue recommendations for the application of a estimator to produce costing of greater detail; incorporate estimator into project team - manage performance of estimating tasks/deliverables.Evaluate project scope and client needs to develop and present recommended budgets for necessary pre-bid and pre-construction cost estimating and cost planning services. Partner with project team to source and oversee the pre-bid and pre-construction services associated with the development of a project budget and cost plan.If you would like to apply for this position, please email your resume to ian.crosby@resourcinggroup.us or call 646 515 1796 to discuss in more detail.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Estimator</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>719</id>
        <date>2019-09-06 15:36:11</date>
        <title>MEP Senior Estimator - Manhattan - $180k</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=719&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Manhattan, New York</location>
        <description>
            MEP Senior Estimator - Manhattan - $180kI am currently working with a long standing, leading New York GC, who are looking to hire a Senior MEP Estimator to strengthen the Pre-Construction Team.My client is a leader and innovator in open shop construction of large-scale and high-rise developments, complex renovations and build-outs of sustainable and uniquely designed spaces. Based in New York City, they have been established nearly 20 years and provides construction management at-risk, design-assist and advisory services with a collaborative, open forum style of management.Essential Requirements:Prepare quantity take-offs, analysis, estimates, and studies for all Mechanical/Plumbing/Fire Protection/Electrical/Technology/LV System (MEP) items incorporated in the assigned scope from conceptual design through completed construction documents. Preliminary design work may be required to complete conceptual estimates.Discuss project approach with pursuit team, operations, safety and quality to better estimate each project.Perform additional assignments per supervisor's direction.Familiarity with New York City Trade Contractors.Knowledge of NYC building codes.Bachelor's Degree in Mechanical, Electrical, or related field from an accredited institution and 10 years estimating &amp; cost control related experience and/or training.Must know all disciplines of the trade including; HVAC, Plumbing, Electrical, Fire ProtectionAbility to estimate all MEPS trades.This is a fantastic opportunity for any MEP Estimator to forward there career, and work for a people friendly company with excellent benefits.Salary Range from - $170k - $180k (Experience Depending)If you would like to apply for this position, please email your resume to ian.crosby@resourcinggroup.us or call 646 515 1796 to discuss in more detail.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Estimator</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>718</id>
        <date>2019-09-06 15:12:30</date>
        <title>Senior Estimator - White Plains - NY - $150k</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=718&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>White Plains, New York</location>
        <description>
            Senior Estimator - White Plains - NY - $150kMy client are one of the fastest growing civil engineering contractors in New York, the role will be based in the Head office near White Plains. They are looking to recruit a reputable Senior Estimator to work along the Estimating Director. The ideal candidate will be knowledgeable with the means and methods with clearing, demo, earthworks, underground utilities, Paving, site concrete. They would have worked on projects to the value of $20million and ideally have local knowledge around the New York area, with experience on ground down site / excavation projects. My clients team up with numerous local architects, engineers, and multiple municipalities on various projects. In addition to there general contracting services, this construction leading firm has a complete site work division; they own and operate an extensive fleet of trucks, heavy machinery and drilling equipment, self-performing all site work. My client offer a competitive compensation package with benefits tailored to the skills, experience, and contribution of the candidate. They are looking to pay up $150k as a base salary If you would like to discuss this position in more detail or apply for the position, please email me on ian.crosby@resourcinggroup.us with an updated resume or call 646 515 1796 to discuss.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Estimator</category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>717</id>
        <date>2019-09-04 21:13:01</date>
        <title>Regional Business Development Manager - Facilities</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=717&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>New York, New York</location>
        <description>
            Job Title: Regional Business Development Manager (Facilities)Location: New York CitySalary: $125,000 to $150,000 + car allowance, 28 days vacation and full benefit package + bonus schemeStart Date: October 2019Job Type: Permanent, Full time Resourcing Group is working in partnership with a global facilities management service provider who is looking to hire for the position Regional Business Development Manager Main Responsibilities: You will lead the business development activities for the regionGenerate new sales revenue for the facilities management companyAchieve the regions growth targets in line with the company's growth projectionsDevise new strategies for targeting new clientsSetting targets for the region and overseeing the bid teamActing as a key contact for potential customer accounts within facilities managementWorking with the marketing team to devise marketing materials and toolsUndertaking regular reviews and performance appraisals for the region Essential Requirements: A Bachelor's degree in Business, Engineering or related10 years minimum experience in a similar senior business development roleStrong business development, operational and marketing skillsProven record in generating new business and achieving revenue growthNegotiation skills and pitching for new businessTravel up to 40% required Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Property & Facilities Management - Director </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>716</id>
        <date>2019-09-04 20:46:17</date>
        <title>Gas Regulatory Compliance Manager</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=716&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Jacksonville, Florida</location>
        <description>
            Job Title: Fuel Regulatory Compliance managerLocation: Jacksonville, FloridaSalary: $65,000 to $85,000 + car allowance, 28 days vacation and full benefit packageStart Date: September or October 2019Job Type: Permanent, Full time Resourcing Group is working in partnership with a global facilities management service provider who is looking to hire for the position Fuel Regulatory Compliance Manager. Main Responsibilities: The successful candidate will manage and monitor fuel regulatory requirements on state and federal levelsEngage federal and state policy makers on current and future policies relevant to the companyEnsures all credits and tax benefits are captured and recorded by working with the renewable fuels teamPartners with mid-office to ensure all renewable energy credits are processed accordinglyWork with Front Office on emerging markets created by regulatory and tax changesEnsure compliance with the environmental credits related to renewable fuelsResearches regulatory changes and communicate with legal and front/mid/back office on necessary updatesOversea processes for quarterly and annual RFS attestationsOversea processes regarding RINs transfer requirementsCompile and submit state / federal regulatory reports, including but not limited to, DOE, EIA, and EPAManage fuel compliance obligations Essential Requirements: A Bachelor's degree in business or related10 years minimum experience in the energy industryTravel up to 80% required5 years experience working in a similar role in retailResourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Maintenance Manager
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>713</id>
        <date>2019-08-26 17:03:37</date>
        <title>Facilities Coordinator</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=713&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>50,001 – 75,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Denver, Colorado</location>
        <description>
            Job Title: Facilities Coordinator Salary: $50,000 to $55,000 + full benefits and bonus Location: Denver, Colorado Job Type: Permanent, Monday to Friday 8:00am to 17:00pmStart Date: 23rd September / ASAP Resourcing Group is working in partnership with a global investment management firm in Denver, Colorado.They are looking to hire an experienced Facilities Coordinator who will provide highly professional and efficient facilities management services to this corporate client. Main Responsibilities:* Effectively managing vendors and support the facilities management team, conduct walk-throughs and inspections* Assist in office move management, event planning, conference room booking, purchasing consumables * Meet and greet guests ensuring your communication is of the highest standards at all times* Ensure guests are connected with their host and are aware of the safety protocols on site* Support the business with front of house security, keep accurate records and administration work as required.* Creates purchase requisitions/orders and process invoices ensuring proper cost center coding.* Prepare conference rooms, catering and clean up post meetings* Coordinate meeting room bookings and ensure all requests are included in conference room calendars* Work with the FM team on service tickets SLAs, administrative support, producing reports and analayzing results Essential Requirements:* High School Diploma or GED* 3 years facilities management experience minimum* Established network in the FM industry To apply for this post, please respond to this advert by sending us your most up to date resume or contact Jayde Edgley on 646 595 7464 or 646 846 6634 Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Facilities Co-ordinator
        </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>712</id>
        <date>2019-08-23 20:33:25</date>
        <title>Scheduler - Frederick - Maryland - $140k</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=712&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Maryland, Maryland</location>
        <description>
            Scheduler - Frederick - Maryland - $140kMy client is seeking an experienced Scheduler with a strong technical knowledge in schedule management to consult at program level (overseeing many projects) in all areas of scheduling from preconstruction to close out. The role will work directly with our Pharma client's cost management/project controls team and construction manager. The individual must have a good understanding of the contractual clauses as it applies to planning and scheduling. Ability to understand and accurately interpret construction documents (drawings, specifications, contracts/general conditions) at all levels of design.This is an exceptional opportunity for a Scheduler who is looking to join a premier global consulting firm and support a construction program. This position is working with one of the leading global Pharmaceutical company's . You will be a forefront of the leading the project, working closely with all stake holders.My client is a leading global cost consultancy, with over 20 offices around the world. Providing professional consultancy services, management support and strategic advice to the global construction industry. From initial concept to project completion, we have been helping clients to build their business. They have developed long-lasting relationships with some of the biggest companies in the world, earning a reputation as a leader in our field.Role and Responsibilities:Implement best practices and reporting trends both internally and externallyCreate and analyze project schedules using Primavera P6Create, manage, and oversee schedules using critical path methodAbility to produce high level and 1, 3, and 6 month look ahead from P6 for reportingWork with contractors and sub-contractors on daily basisPrepare and update monthly progress reportsActively monitor and communicate any possible project issues that could delay the scheduleWork closely with various disciplines in the project team to ensure schedule accuracy and advise project management on possible issues Desired Experience and Education: Bachelor's degree in an engineering discipline or equivalent10 + years of experience in commercial and industrial construction in project controls (Planning and Scheduling, EVA)Prefer experience in biotechnology and pharmaceutical industries. Experience in other related industries are acceptablePrimavera P6 and Excel expert useAbility to work independently is crucialPackage: Circa $140k basic salary (Negotiable, depending on experience)10% bonus (Performance dependent)Additional benefits401KHealthcare Please email your resume to ian.crosby@resourcinggroup.us or call +1 646 515 1796 to discuss the position. I have a full Job Description for you to review.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - K-12 Project Manager </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>711</id>
        <date>2019-08-23 20:19:17</date>
        <title>
            Senior Project Manager - Frederick - Maryland - $140k
        </title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=711&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Maryland, Maryland</location>
        <description>
            Senior Project Manager - Frederick - Maryland - $140k My client are looking for a Senior Project Manager to manage a large scale Pharmaceutical construction projects for clients and taking responsibility for the delivery of the project(s) on time, within budget and to the satisfaction of the client and all stakeholders. The Senior Project Manager will be responsible for monitoring the day-to-day activities in the field, managing and coordinating the flow of information and reporting and tracking issues arising from progress, quality and safety. The successful candidate will be client facing with proven communication and organisational skills.This is an exceptional opportunity for a Senior Project Manager who is looking to join a premier global consulting firm and support a construction program. This position is working with one of the leading global Pharmaceutical company's . You will be a forefront of the leading the project, working closely with all stake holders.My client is a leading global cost consultancy, with over 20 offices around the world. Providing professional consultancy services, management support and strategic advice to the global construction industry. From initial concept to project completion, we have been helping clients to build their business. They have developed long-lasting relationships with some of the biggest companies in the world, earning a reputation as a leader in our field.Key requirements: 10 years experience working in a PM roleDegree qualified in Project Management, Engineering, Quantity Surveying or similar construction related disciplineChartered or seeking Chartered Project Manager statusManage a range of projects for several clients, delivering all projects to schedule, within budget and meeting all reporting requirementsPrepare RFP for design team members and the main contractor, in conjunction with the project quantity surveyor, issue of same, evaluate returns, interview potential members and recommend selections to the client Package: Circa $120k basic salary (Negotiable, depending on experience)10% bonus (Performance dependent)Additional benefits401KHealthcare Please email your resume to ian.crosby@resourcinggroup.us or call +1 646 515 1796 to discuss the position. I have a full Job Description for you to review.Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>Construction - Project Manager </category>
    </job>
    <job>
        <id>710</id>
        <date>2019-08-23 14:23:05</date>
        <title>Health and Safety Facilities Assistant</title>
        <url>
            https://www.resourcinggroup.us/index.php?option=com_recmgr&view=job&jid=710&Itemid=986
        </url>
        <salary>>90,000</salary>
        <jobtype>Permanent</jobtype>
        <location>Newark, New Jersey</location>
        <description>
            Job Title: Health and Safety Facilities AssistantLocation: New Jersey Salary: $60,000 to $80,000 Resourcing Group is working in partnership with a Global Facilities Management service provider who is looking to hire an experienced Health and Safety Facilities Assistant. Main Responsibilities: Supporting the facility teams on executing their facility services and managing subcontractors in accordance with quality, health, safety, environment and wellbeing standards and processes (QHSEW) including ISO9001, ISO14001 and OSHAS18001 certifications.Tendering contracts with Vendors to ensure best pricing and services.Managing and mentoring a customer centric staff between multi-facilitiesPartnering with senior facilities coordinator for completion of ISO 14001 program.Managing the implementation of health and safety representatives, regulatory H&amp;S risk-assessments, H&amp;S committee meetings, first-aid and fire marshals, evacuations, ergonomics/DSE among others) and assisting with account QHSE compliance registers.Managing the roll-out of new health and safety programs to cover client staff and facilities management services.Assisting in the prequalification of new and existing supply chain.Assisting in the creation and coordination of the account annual audit and inspection schedule, undertaking and providing support for operational audits as required.Training of staff, in all areas of QHSE to ensure competence of account team.Liaising with colleagues to develop, reviewing and maintaining standards for processes and proceduresCoordinating the QHSE meetings, forums, ensure attendance and produce minutes as required.Assisting with the monthly QHSE reportsEvaluating results of reporting, audits, corrective actions and operational reports.Communicating and supporting the account QHSE KPIs, objectives and targets.Directing the incident investigations, ensuring all associated paperwork is completed on time, preparing alerts and action findings.Managing and delivering both on line DSE risk assessment system and face to face DSE risk assessments. Essential Requirements: * Bachelor's Degree in Facilities Management or Engineering or equivalent* OSHA Certification* At least 2 years Facilities experiencePrevious experience in a similar position overseeing a global account is essentialWorking knowledge of OSHA and 30 certificationFinancial services experienceTo apply for this post, please respond to this advert by sending us your most up to date resume or contact Jayde Edgley on 646 846 6634 Resourcing Group is acting as an Employment Agency in relation to this vacancy.
        </description>
        <category>
            Property & Facilities Management - Assistant Facilities Manager
        </category>
    </job>
</jobs>
